<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>

<!--
	FACTION DESCRIPTIONS
-->

	<string id="st_faction_stalker">
		<text>Loner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_stalker_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Loners, or free stalkers, prefer to remain unaligned with the various factions operating in the Zone.\n
		The vast majority of the Zone's inhabitants belong to this unofficial brotherhood, choosing to live life without getting caught up in the ideals of others.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]RECOMMENDED FOR:%c[ui_gray_2] New Players
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_bandit">
		<text>Bandit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_bandit_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Chernobyl's outlaws know that while Ukraine and Belarus control the Zone on paper, it is in effect a lawless place.Bandits are killers, thieves and other members of the criminal underworld who exploit this fact, abusing the Zone's anarchic state to hide from the law and continue their illicit dealings.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_dolg">
		<text>Duty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_dolg_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Duty is a paramilitary group, whose members live by a clear military charter. The ideology of the faction is to protect mankind from the dangers of the Zone and ultimately fight for its destruction. Duty is often set out to deal with the internal problems of the Zone, including mutants, anarchists and bandits. They are said to be funded by the government as they and the military have common goals: to contain, explore and destroy the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_freedom">
		<text>Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_freedom_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]An anarchist group consisting mainly of free stalkers, the faction's goal is to preserve the Zone as a free territory and oppose the monopoly of the authorities. Although the group declares itself to be anarchist. Freedomers believe that the Zone cannot be defeated, and people should co-exist with it, seeing it as a great opportunity for research and study. They also believe that the Zone should not be hidden from the rest of the world. The emblems they have on their suits says "Воля", which means "Freedom" in Ukrainian and Russian.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_army">
		<text>Military</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_army_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The Military refers to the Ukrainian government's internal troops, Spetsnaz detachments and commissioned stalkers.\n
		They guard the Zone from infiltration of unauthorized persons, taking a hardline approach to securing the border between the Zone and the outside world, they're known to shoot all unsanctioned personnel on sight. Soldiers have the right to shoot without warning because all unofficial persons in the Zone are considered "illegal" and legally allowed to be eliminated. They have no ideology as such and can be very corrupt. In addition, they are in charge of providing food and protection for the scientists.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_ecolog">
		<text>Ecologist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_ecolog_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Sponsored by the Ukrainian government, the Ecologists are an official body of scientists and contracted field assistants who research the Zone, hoping to harness its potential for the good of mankind. Of all the Zone's factions, the Ecologists are the generally the most neutral, with their only real focus being on the pursuit of knowledge and science.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]RECOMMENDED FOR:%c[ui_gray_2] Pacifistics
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_killer">
		<text>Mercenary</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_killer_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Mercenaries in the Zone usually belong to a semi-loose company of professional fighters. These irregulars come from all sorts of nationalities and backgrounds, selling their services as veteran soldiers to anyone willing to pay and are known to kill anyone who gets in their way. Often carrying out contracted kills and robberies, most stalkers try not to cross paths with them unless necessary or desperate.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_monolith">
		<text>Monolith</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_monolith_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]A religious cult that is hostile to all but their own, the Monolithians believe in the power of the Wish Granter, rumored to be an alien artefact hidden in the center of the Zone. Members of this faction devote their lives to protecting the secret of the Great Crystal, ensuring that no one ever reaches the center of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]RECOMMENDED FOR:%c[ui_gray_2] Advanced Players
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_csky">
		<text>Clear Sky</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_csky_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]An independent scientific and paramilitary organization, dedicated to increasing the general understanding of the Zone while safeguarding its deadliest secrets. Although the group effectively collapsed after a failed expedition to the CNPP seven years ago, the few remaining survivors eventually rebuilt the faction to its former stature.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]RECOMMENDED FOR:%c[ui_gray_2] New Players
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_renegade">
		<text>Renegade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_renegade_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The faction consists mainly of Bandits not organized under Yoga's lead and stalkers that broke off from other factions. The Renegades do not seem to be under a formal leadership and act as warbands and gangs instead. Most Renegades have committed transgressions so grave that no group will take them in, and even bandits just barely tolerate them.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]RECOMMENDED FOR:%c[ui_gray_2] Advanced Players
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_greh">
		<text>Sin</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_greh_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Sin are an extremely hostile cult of mutant stalkers who believe in the divine essence of the Zone. Often described as zombified or possessed, these "dark stalkers" of the ominous Sin faction seek to expand the Zone to the rest of the world and they will stop at nothing to accomplish this ambitious goal.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]RECOMMENDED FOR:%c[ui_gray_2] Advanced Players
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_isg">
		<text>UNISG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_isg_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The United Nations International Scientific Group is a special forces unit with a keen interest in the Zone. Whatever their goal may be, their field agents are far from defenceless, and most would rather shoot first than risk information on their movements getting leaked.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]RECOMMENDED FOR:%c[ui_gray_2] Advanced Players
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_faction_zombied">
		<text>Zombified</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_faction_zombied_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Braaaiiinnnsss!!!\n
		Zombified stalkers are mindless husks, reduced to the most basic animal-like instincts and will attack almost anything that gets too close.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]RECOMMENDED FOR:%c[ui_gray_2] Masochists
		</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	INFO
-->

	<string id="st_mm_list_economy_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Progression difficulty has a big impact on the economy, which affects the player's progression during their journey in the Zone.\n
		Aspects affected range from sell/buy prices with traders, repair/upgrade prices with mechanics, rarity of loot, money and goodwill earned by completing tasks.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can control each one of these aspects in your playthrough at any time.\n
		See "Extra Options -> Progression Difficulty".
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_list_difficulty_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Gameplay difficulty affects aspects such as protection against damage sources, stamina loss and carry weight, in addition to things such as water and sleep deprivation.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can control each one of these aspects in your playthrough at any time.\n
		See "Extra Options -> Gameplay difficulty".
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_story_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Story mode allows the player to experience a unique set of story-driven and dynamic questlines.\n 
		Note that story-driven questlines such as "Living Legend", "Mortal Sin" and "Operation Afterglow" are only available to Loner, Duty, Freedom, Ecologist, Mercenary and Clear Sky factions.\n
		However, dynamic questlines can be enjoyed by all playable factions. In both cases, speak to your faction leader to begin. Have fun!\n \n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Warfare mode.\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Survival mode.\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Azazel mode.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_drx_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]A dynamic, linked set of varied tasks to take you throughout the Zone.\n
		Infinite replayability!\n \n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Story mode.\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Azazel mode.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_hardcore_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Removes your game saves upon death.\n
		You are free to make as many saves as you wish but dying will result in the removal of all saves made with that character.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_hardcore_aim_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Maximizes AI aim predictability, making it more difficult for the player to dodge hits while moving.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_survival_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Replaces all spawns with Zombies.\n
			These hordes will make their way to your location. Be prepared and see how long you can survive!\n \n
			%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Warfare mode.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_azazel_mode_desc">
		<text>
			%c[ui_gray_2]Death is not the end!\n
			Like the demon Azazel, you will possess a new body when you die by taking over the form of another random stalker that is currently existing within the Zone.\n
			If you have companions, you will become one of them. This feature compliments Ironman and/or Survival mode very well.\n \n
			%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]All maps will be unlocked in Azazel mode.\n
			%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Story mode.\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_warfare_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]TGrants stalker's A-Life system more freedom, creating a more dynamic Zone.\n
		Faction ownership of bases and territories is more prone to change. Medics, traders and mechanics are now also replaceable.\n
		You have the ability to lead your faction and help them with taking over the surrounding areas, achieving dominance in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Command your faction through the PDA map.\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Story mode.\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Not compatible with Survival mode.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_campfire_desc">
		<text>%c[pda_white](%c[ui_red]LEAVE UNCHECKED - 'Better Campfire Saves' mod handles this%c[pda_white])\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_conditions_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Prevents saving progress if you're:\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Injured\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Bleeding\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Irradiated\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]In combat with enemies\n
		%c[ui_red]• %c[ui_gray_2]Under circumstances of an emission or psi-storm\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]All hardcore save modes are compatible with each other.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_ck_routes_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Many levels are not accessible by default.\n
		Hidden routes can be discovered throughout your playthrough.\n
		Enabling this option will unlock all levels upon starting a new game.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_list_hardcore_lives_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]An additional feature for Ironman mode that allows you to set how many lives you have at the beginning of a new game.\n
		Every time you die, you lose a life.\n
		Once out of lives, all game saves of the current playthrough will be removed.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ironman mode must be active.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_list_hardcore_regen_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]An additional feature for Ironman mode that allows you to set how many days it takes to grant an extra life.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Sleeping will not help.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ironman mode must be active.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_list_timer_desc">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]You can only save your game after a specific amount of time has passed.\n
		Once you save your game, you cannot make another save again until the timer is over again.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]All hardcore save modes are compatible with each other.
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	UNUSED
-->

	<string id="st_mm_box_faction_desc">
		<text>
			%c[ui_gray_2]%s flair.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_box_icon_desc">
		<text>
			%c[ui_gray_2]The portrait of your character.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_list_map_desc">
		<text>
			%c[ui_gray_2]Choose the start location of your new game.
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_ck_reset_desc">
		<text>
			%c[ui_gray_2]Reset the inventory.
		</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	HEADERS
-->

	<string id="st_mm_new_game_character">
		<text>Character</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_faction">
		<text>Select Faction</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_icon">
		<text>Select Portrait</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_options">
		<text>Options</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_inventory">
		<text>INVENTORY</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_loadout">
		<text>LOADOUT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_name">
		<text>NAME:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_faction_2">
		<text>Faction:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_money">
		<text>MONEY:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_points_left">
		<text>POINTS:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_points_used">
		<text>POINTS USED:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_st_random_location">
		<text>Random Location</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mm_new_game_relations">
		<text>RELATIONS:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_description">
		<text>BRIEF HISTORY:</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_points">
		<text>Points</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_new_game_essential">
		<text>Essential</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Hint -->
	<string id="st_mm_itm_desc_unknown">
		<text>No available info</text>
	</string>
	
	<!-- Options -->
	<string id="st_cap_check_warfare">
		<text>Warfare</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_check_drx">
		<text>DoctorX Questlines</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_check_campfire">
		<text>(DON'T TOUCH)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_check_conditions">
		<text>Agony Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_list_timer">
		<text>Timer Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_check_routes">
		<text>Accessible Zone</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_list_hardcore_lives">
		<text>Ironman Lives</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_list_hardcore_regen">
		<text>Life Granter</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_cap_list_difficulty">
		<text>Gameplay Difficulty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_list_economy">
		<text>Progression Difficulty</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_econ_1">
		<text>Tourist (Easy)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_econ_2">
		<text>Scavenger (Medium)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_econ_3">
		<text>Survivalist (Hard)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_diff_1">
		<text>Rookie (Easy)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_diff_2">
		<text>Stalker (Medium)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_diff_3">
		<text>Veteran (Hard)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_diff_4">
		<text>Master (Hardcore)</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_off">
		<text>off</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_game_min">
		<text>min.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_game_mins">
		<text>mins.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_game_hour">
		<text>hour</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_game_hours">
		<text>hours</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_game_day">
		<text>day</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_game_days">
		<text>days</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_game_life">
		<text>life</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_new_game_lives">
		<text>lives</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	BUTTONS
-->

	<string id="st_mm_btn_new_game_faction">
		<text>FACTION</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_btn_new_game_icon">
		<text>PORTRAIT</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_btn_new_game_back">
		<text>BACK</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_btn_new_game_submit">
		<text>START</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mm_btn_new_game_rand">
		<text>RANDOMIZE</text>
	</string>

<!--
	DISCORD
-->

	<string id="st_hardcore_lives_left">
		<text>Lives Left</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hardcore_lives_left_single">
		<text>Life Left</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_player_dead">
		<text>Dead</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_main_menu">
		<text>Main Menu</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_loading">
		<text>Loading</text> 
	</string>
	<string id="st_pause_menu">
		<text>Pause Menu</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cap_check_freeplay">
		<text>Freeplay Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_azazel_lives_possessed">
		<text>Lives Possessed</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_azazel_lives_possessed_single">
		<text>Life Possessed</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_godmode">
		<text>God Mode</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>