<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>

	<string id="encyclopedia_features">
		<text>Features</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_azazel_mode">
		<text>Azazel Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_azazel_mode_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Azazel Mode%c[ui_gray_2]allows you to continue playing as another character after death.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]In Azazel mode, death is not the end. Upon the demise of your character, you will posses the body of a random stalker who was previously controlled by the AI.\n \n
		Should you have companions at the time of your death, they will be given priority and you will continue playing as one of them instead.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_ironman_mode">
		<text>Ironman Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_ironman_mode_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Ironman Mode %c[ui_gray_2]adds an indirect layer of difficulty to gameplay, whereby all of your saved games for a character are deleted upon their death.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]You can customize your Ironman run on new game setup, such as the maximum number of deaths before your save games get deleted.\n \n
		The life granting feature will revert one death count after a certain amount of time so that players can have a chance to survive more deaths over time.\n \n
		When playing with this mode enabled, all the saves you make will be uniquely tagged as its own Ironman playthrough. As such, it is impossible for unrelated saves to be deleted by mistake.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_story_mode">
		<text>Story Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_story_mode_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Story Mode%c [ui_gray_1]introduces the player to "Lost of the Zone" storylines, in addition to faction questlines that can be completed separately.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information
		%c[ui_gray_2]Talk to your faction leader about the recent events in the Zone and they should give you info and leads.\n \n
		%c[pda_red]This mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Availability\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Clear Sky\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Duty\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ecologist\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Freedom\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Loner\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Mercenary\n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Faction questlines can be done for all factions, as long as Story mode is active. Players of bonus factions can complete those questlines by speaking to the leader of a friendly faction, if found.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_warfare">
		<text>Warfare</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_warfare_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Warfare %c[ui_gray_2]simulates a dynamic war as each faction struggles to dominate the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Warfare lets the player assume control of their faction. This is done at run time, and the player can choose between either the dynamic expansion system or the manual expansion system. The dynamic expansion system will adapt to any bases you captured in manual expansion mode when you switch back.\n \n
		With an offline combat simulator, squads can intercept other squads arbitrarily, so the Zone will be much more dynamic and large scale war will rage at the far corners of the map.\n \n
		A dynamic expansion system adapts to changes on the simulation board and ensures no playthrough will be entirely the same.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This mode was originally created by "%c[pda_white]werejew%c[ui_gray_2]" for %c[pda_white]Call of Chernobyl%c[ui_gray_2].
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_survival_mode">
		<text>Survival Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_survival_mode_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Survival Mode %c[ui_gray_2]turns the Zone into a hunting ground where %c[pda_white]you %c[ui_gray_2]are the prey.\n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With this mode enabled, all spawns are replaced with zombified stalkers and mutants who will slowly stumble towards your location in an attempt to kill you.\n \n
		Featuring a more prominent role are zombies; the last devolution of zombified stalkers who have lost the ability to operate mechanical devices such as firearms.\n \n
		Only a few traders and stalker squads can be found, meaning you will have to survive off of what you can scavenge in the world.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_campfire_mode">
		<text>Campfire Saves Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_campfire_mode_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Campfire Saves Mode %c[ui_gray_2]prevents you from saving your progress unless you're standing close to a campfire.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]To save your progress in Campfire mode, approach a nearby campfire, then save your game as usual.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_agony_mode">
		<text>Agony Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_agony_mode_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Agony Mode %c[ui_gray_2]adds another layer of difficulty by preventing you from saving your progress based on certain criteria.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[pda_white]You cannot save your progress in Agony mode if you're:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Injured\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Bleeding\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Irradiated\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]In Combat\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Emission\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Psi-storm
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_timer_mode">
		<text>Timer Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_timer_mode_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Timer Mode %c[ui_gray_2] restricts players to saving only after a specific amount of time.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This mode can only be enabled from the character creation screen.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_companions">
		<text>Companions</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_companions_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Companions %c[ui_gray_2]are stalkers who can be recruited to your side, similar to followers and familiars in other games.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With the Zone being as dangerous as it is, most stalkers can be found exploring in small groups, usually in sizes of 3 to 4.\n \n
		This feature allows you to do the same, as by talking to the leader of one of these groups you may be able to convince them to explore the Zone together with you.\n \n
		The only requirements are that the squad's leader must have friendly relations with you, their rank be no more than a single tier above yours and that you do not have too many stalkers already following you.\n \n
		In very special cases, some characters may be used as companions to help complete certain tasks. These have their own unique set of requirements and do not count towards your squad limit.\n \n
		Information about your companions can be viewed in the 'Relations' tab of the PDA, where you can also issue them orders individually or as a group, as well as change their behavior. An option is available to show Companions info on the HUD.\n \n
		This can also be done through key-bindings, which can be set via the '%c[pda_white]Controls%c[ui_gray_2]' options menu.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_guide">
		<text>Guide</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_guide_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Guide %c[ui_gray_2]is a resource to help teach you about the game and its contents.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature was added at much request by players to help explain features and gameplay mechanics, as well as to add a visual representation of your progression.\n \n
		Articles are sorted by category, with all tutorial-esque and important content being unlocked after creating your character.\n \n
		When you unlock an article, its name and category are displayed in the message, allowing you to find the content with relative ease.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_hud">
		<text>HUD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_hud_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]HUD %c[ui_gray_2]displays various indicators regarding the state of your health and equipment.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[pda_white]State %c[ui_gray_2]indicators display the current state of your health and equipment. A grey indicator is shown if the state is slightly bad, while yellow indicates a cause for concern. Orange and red denote critical states.\n
		%c[pda_white]Danger %c[ui_gray_2]indicators are shown when you enter a dangerous zone which has a direct effect on your health or equipment. The more critical the color, the more severe the health drain you'll experience.\n
		%c[pda_white]Boosting %c[ui_gray_2]indicators are shown as long as you're under the effect of a consumable's positive effects. Typically, these effects will be some form of healing, protection or regeneration. All indicators disappear when the related effect wears off.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_map_spots">
		<text>Map Spots</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_map_spots_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Map Spots%c[ui_gray_2] are icons which appear on the map to highlight points of particular interest.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Many locations and entities have map spots associated with them, making it easier to read the map at a glance without having to worry about remembering tons of information.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Toggles\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Anomalous areas, important people and objects (traders, technicians, beds, etc.), stashes, and task waypoints can be toggled within the PDA by pressing the aptly named buttons at the top of the map tab.\n \n
		Regardless of these settings, those which are attributed to stalkers and other moving objects are always visible on your minimap as there is no guarantee they will remain stationary and in a single location.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_rank">
		<text>Rank</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_rank_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Rank %c[ui_gray_2]is a score system based on what a stalker has accomplished in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Actions which you perform throughout your playthrough are recorded and each grants a varying number of points depending on the action.\n \n
		As you accumulate more points, your rank will gradually change as you pass through each milestone, with milestones requiring an additional 1,000 points on top of the requirements of its predecessor.\n \n
		Most of these actions are logged in the statistics tab of the PDA, which also contains an in-game leaderboard that keeps track of the current 100 highest-ranking stalkers.\n \n
		The higher your rank, the more gravity you will have amongst common stalkers. While this means you can recruit more skilled companions, it also means those who oppose you will start sending others to ensure you are...taken care of. Beware.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Ranks\n
		%c[pda_white]• Rookie: %c[ui_gray_2]0\n
		%c[pda_white]• Trainee: %c[ui_gray_2]2000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Experienced: %c[ui_gray_2]4000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Professional: %c[ui_gray_2]7000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Veteran: %c[ui_gray_2]10,000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Expert: %c[ui_gray_2]15,000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Master: %c[ui_gray_2]21,000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Legend: %c[ui_gray_2]28,000
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_reputation">
		<text>Reputation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_reputation_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Reputation %c[ui_gray_2]is a representation of how a stalker interacts with others.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Reputation is similar to rank but differs in that it isn't quite so linear - being able to both increase or decrease based on your interactions with other stalkers rather than the environment.\n \n
		The easiest ways to increase reputation are by completing tasks, providing first-aid to those in need and killing your faction's enemies. Inversely, the easiest ways to lose reputation are by cancelling or failing tasks and killing neutral or friendly stalkers.\n \n
		It should be noted that whilst it is used by some features, reputation is largely immersion-focused and should not be confused with goodwill.\n \n
		The lower your reputation, the more other members of your faction and their friends will hate you. In extreme cases, they might even begin plotting your death.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Reputations\n
		%c[pda_white]• Terrible: %c[ui_gray_2]-2000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Dreary: %c[ui_gray_2]-1500\n
		%c[pda_white]• Awful: %c[ui_gray_2]-1000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Bad: %c[ui_gray_2]-500\n
		%c[pda_white]• Neutral: %c[ui_gray_2]0\n
		%c[pda_white]• Good: %c[ui_gray_2]500\n
		%c[pda_white]• Great: %c[ui_gray_2]1000\n
		%c[pda_white]• Brilliant: %c[ui_gray_2]1500\n
		%c[pda_white]• Excellent: %c[ui_gray_2]2000
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_stashes">
		<text>Stashes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_stashes_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Stashes %c[ui_gray_2]are items stored by stalkers in often well-hidden locations.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Most stalkers in the Zone store spare ammunition, food, and medicine in containers, backpacks and other hidden objects with the intent to retrieve them later.\n \n
		Frequently, the information as to their whereabouts die with the stalker who hid them, resulting in numerous stashes full of unused items strewing the landscape waiting to be discovered at any time.\n \n
		Information brokers and traders often give coordinates to stashes as a bonus payment for those who have done good work.\n \n
		You can create your own stashes by %c[pda_white]right-clicking %c[ui_gray_2]and selecting the appropriate option on any backpack in your inventory.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Notes\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Stashes which you create are never looted by other stalkers, so your items will always be safe.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Identification
		%c[ui_gray_2]The type and/or status of a stash can be easily determined by looking at its icon on the map or by hovering your mouse cursor over it.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Green: %c[ui_gray_2]Untouched\n
		%c[pda_white]• Purple: %c[ui_gray_2]Unique\n
		%c[pda_white]• Red: %c[ui_gray_2]Emergency\n
		%c[pda_white]• Yellow: %c[ui_gray_2]Player-owned
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_workshop">
		<text>Workshop</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_workshop_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Mechanic's Workshop%c[ui_gray_2] allows the player to repair/upgrade and craft equipment on their own.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Every mechanic in the Zone uses their workshop/vice for proper repair and upgrade services. Some experienced stalkers prefer to do such work on their own. Therefore, many temporarily rent a workshop from its owner to tweak their own equipment.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]With a workshop and proper tools, the following is possible:\n
		%c[pda_white]• Repair (Part Replacement): %c[ui_gray_2]Every weapon or outfit is made of specific parts and components. When they get damaged, you can use counterparts to replace the old, damaged ones and improve the condition of your equipment.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Upgrade:  %c[ui_gray_2]With the right tools, you can install upgrades for your equipment.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Craft: %c[ui_gray_2]With the right components/parts and enough knowledge, it's possible to craft a variaty of items.\n \n
		When you use a workshop, a list of main tools will be shown along with their availability (your possession, or owned by the mechanic). These tools are required for crafting and upgrading.\n \n
		An info bar is shown at the bottom to assist the player with necessary steps to work on the workshop.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_workshop_repair">
		<text>Workshop (Repair/Parts)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_workshop_repair_text">
		<text>A %c[pda_white]Mechanic's Workshop %c[ui_gray_2]can be used to repair damaged weapons or outfits by replacing damaged parts with counterparts of better condition.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Each weapon or outfit is made of a set of components/parts. The total condition of an item is summed up by the condition of its individual parts.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Weapon parts have 4 states of condition:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_red]Deformed\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[d_orange]Damaged\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[0,250,250,0]Scratched\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[d_green]Functional\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Outfit parts have 4 states of condition:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_red]Torn\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[d_orange]Damaged\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[0,250,250,0]Scratched\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[d_green]Clean\n \n
		%c[pda_white]To repair equipment, you need the following items:\n
		%c[pda_white]• Suitable Repair Toolkits: %c[ui_gray_2]Such toolkits are sold by mechanics.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Identical Counterparts (with better condition): %c[ui_gray_2]These can be acquired by disassembling weapons and outfits.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Repair Procedures\n
		%c[pda_white]1) %c[ui_gray_2]Check the requirements to repair your equipment first. When you have the tools and at least one better counterpart, the part buttons will be active.\n
		%c[pda_white]2) %c[ui_gray_2]Click on one of the highlighted parts. The part pickup list will be updated with the counterparts you have in your inventory.\n
		%c[pda_white]3) %c[ui_gray_2]Inside the part pickup list, click on one of the counterparts with better condition. The main part will be replaced and updated with the new one. This will reflect back on the total condition of your equipment.\n
		%c[pda_white]4) %c[ui_gray_2]Repeat the process as long as you have more parts to replace and enough toolkits.\n
		%c[pda_white]5) %c[ui_gray_2]When you're finally done, press the "Repair" button.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Notes\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Grayed out parts mean that you don't have replacement counterparts of better condition in your inventory, thus you cannot interact with it.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]If you have counterparts to use in replacing your equipment parts, but their condition is not high enough, you can use specific toolkits to repair these parts first before using the workshop such as: %c[pda_white]Multitool, File, Ramrod, Sewing Thread.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Every part replacement requires one use of a suitable repair kit.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_workshop_upgrade">
		<text>Workshop (Upgrade)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_workshop_upgrade_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Mechanic's Workshop %c[ui_gray_2]can be used to upgrade your weapon or outfit by having the proper tools for the job, instead of spending money for mechanics to do the job for you.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The way to upgrade your equipment is similar to any mechanic's upgrading system, but with the requirement of additional tools.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]To Upgrade equipment, you need the following items:\n
		%c[pda_white]• Suitable Repair Toolkits: %c[ui_gray_2]Such toolkits are sold by mechanics.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• Upgrade Toolkits: %c[ui_gray_2] These tools can be found in the possession of other stalkers or as loot in the Zone.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Main Tools: %c[ui_gray_2]Such toolkits are rare to come by, as mechanics always need them for installing upgrades.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Repair Procedures\n
		%c[pda_white]1) %c[ui_gray_2]Check the requirements to upgrade your equipment first. When you have the correct repair kit, you can proceed.\n
		%c[pda_white]2) %c[ui_gray_2]Click on an item you wish to upgrade. The upgrade tree will appear along with any installed upgrades it already has.\n
		%c[pda_white]3) %c[ui_gray_2]Each upgrade requires a specific upgrade toolkit, as shown next the upgrade itself.\n
		%c[pda_white]4) %c[ui_gray_2]If an upgrade is available to install, click on it. Repeat the same procedure if you wish.\n
		%c[pda_white]5) %c[ui_gray_2]When you're finally done, press the "Upgrade" button to install all upgrades you picked.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Notes\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Hover over an upgrade to see all details regarding its properties. It will also show additionl requirements if the upgrade is not available.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Every upgrade requires one use of the suitable repair kit.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_workshop_craft">
		<text>Workshop (Craft)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_workshop_craft_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Mechanic's Workshops %c[ui_gray_2]can be used to craft a variety of items.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Sometimes it's hard to come by some equipment in the Zone. Thus, different materials can come in handy to craft useful equipment.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]To Craft equipment, you need the following items:\n
		%c[pda_white]• Main Tools: %c[ui_gray_2]Such toolkits are rare to come by, as mechanics always need them for installing upgrades.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Guidebooks and Recipes: %c[ui_gray_2]Proper crafting comes with knowledge. Many stalkers might have useful recipes or guidebooks.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Components: %c[ui_gray_2]Each item is made of different materials and components. Such materials can be acquired by disassembling different items.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Repair Procedures\n
		%c[pda_white]1) %c[ui_gray_2]Choose a craft entry. Entries are listed by item type with each showing a list of related items to pick from.\n
		%c[pda_white]2) %c[ui_gray_2]If the item you want to craft is highlighted, it means you know the recipe. Click on it to proceed.\n
		%c[pda_white]3) %c[ui_gray_2]A list of components along with the required toolkit will be shown. The minimum amount of components is shown under the component icon.\n
		%c[pda_white]4) %c[ui_gray_2]If you're missing the main toolkit, or some conponent doesn't meet the minimum requirement, crafting cannot be done.\n
		%c[pda_white]5) %c[ui_gray_2]Otherwise, click on the "%c[pda_white]Craft%c[ui_gray_2]" button to craft the item you wish.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Notes\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Main tools are required to be available for the work, they won't be consumed in the process.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Usable Tools: %c[ui_gray_2]Basic tools, Advanced tools, Expert tools, Drug-making kit, Gunsmithing tools.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]If you've brought toolkits to a mechanic before, they will available at the workshop to use right away.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Disassembly can be done using specific tools, see the related article.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]All recipes will be shown in the corner. Only known recipes will be highlighted.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_disassembly">
		<text>Item Disassembly</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_disassembly_text">
		<text>
		You can %c[pda_white]disassemble %c[ui_gray_2]various types of items to acquire basic parts.\n \n
		\n%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Disassembly helps with recycling unwanted items to acquire parts that can be used for other meaningful purposes such as repairing or crafting other items at the workshop.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]This can be done by using one of the following three tools:\n
		%c[pda_white]• Swiss Knife %c[ui_gray_2](except weapons)\n
		%c[pda_white]• Grooming Kit %c[ui_gray_2](except weapons)\n
		%c[pda_white]• Multitool\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Procedure\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Items that can be disassembled will show a (%c[pda_white]disassemble [!]%c[ui_gray_2]) option when you click on them in your inventory. To disassemble an item, make sure you have a suitable disassembling tool, then hold the '%c[pda_white]Left-ALT%c[ui_gray_2]' button, click on the item you wish to disassemble and then choose (%c[pda_white]disassemble [!]%c[ui_gray_2]).\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Note\n
		%c[ui_gray_2] The '%c[pda_white]Left-ALT%c[ui_gray_2]' button acts as a safety procedure to prevent accidental disassembly. This can be disabled in the settings.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_battery">
		<text>Devices &amp; Batteries</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_battery_text">
		<text>Every %c[pda_white]device %c[ui_gray_2]has its own %c[pda_white]battery %c[ui_gray_2]and they will not function without them.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Device power is represented by a small, blue bar under its icon. When using a device, it will constantly drain power. Once the batteries are completely drained, the device will no longer function.\n \n
		You can pack and unpack batteries from devices. If you have an important device that's low on power, you can always unpack batteries from other unused devices.\n \n
		Power consumption varies between devices. High-end devices tend to drain power faster than lesser types. It's advised to keep extra batteries in your pocket as you never know when you'll need them.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Procedure\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]To put batteries in a device, simply drag and drop the batteries on to the device.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]To unpack batteries from devices, '%c[pda_white]right-click%c[ui_gray_2]' on the device in your inventory then choose the '%c[pda_white]unpack batteries%c[ui_gray_2]' option.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_economy_difficulty">
		<text>Progression Difficulty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_economy_difficulty_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Progression Difficulty %c[ui_gray_2]establishes how harsh the economy is within the Zone and directly influences the progress of your playthough.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Aspects affected by this range from (but are not limited to) sell/buy prices with traders, repair/upgrade prices with mechanics, rarity of loot, money and goodwill earned by completing tasks. You may customise all aspects of Progression Difficulty.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Here's a list of all available options:\n
		%c[pda_white]• Earned Goodwill: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the amount of goodwill earned upon completing tasks.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Money Rewards: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the amount of money earned upon completing tasks.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Repair Costs Coefficient: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the cost of repair services offered by mechanics.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Upgrade Costs Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the cost of upgrade services offered by mechanics.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Trade Prices (Buy) Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the prices of items that traders sell to you.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Trade Prices (Sell) Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the prices of items that traders buy from you.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Loot (Items) Chance Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the chance of finding items on corpses.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Loot (Money) Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the amount of money found on corpses.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Full-percentage Part System: %c[ui_gray_2]When enabled, the parts disassembled from weapons/outfits will have numric conditions, thus making the system more complicated.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Discovering Stash Chance: %c[ui_gray_2]Controls the chance of finding stash locations in PDAs.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Weapon Degradation Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the degradation rate of your weapons.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Battery Power Consumption Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the amount of power consumed from devices on use.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Enable Limited Bolts: %c[ui_gray_2]Makes bolt storage limited.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Enable Artefact Degradation: %c[ui_gray_2]Arterfacts can degrade when they protect their users from relative anomolous damager. Degradation affects artefact price.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Artefact Respawn Chance: %c[ui_gray_2]Chance of artefacts to appear in anomolous fields.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Traders Restock Cycle (Hours): %c[ui_gray_2]Hours until traders restock again.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Economy factors are configured per current playthrough.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Progression factors are only accessible through loaded saves. You can tweak them inside the settings menu.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_gameplay_difficulty">
		<text>Gameplay Difficulty</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_gameplay_difficulty_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Gameplay Difficulty %c[ui_gray_2]establishes how easy or hard the game should be to play.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Gameplay difficulty affects aspects related to the player such as protection against damage sources, stamina loss and carry weight, in addition to other aspects such as water and sleep deprivation. You may customise all aspects of Gameplay Difficulty.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Here's a list of all available options:\n
		%c[pda_white]• Player Protection: %c[ui_gray_2]A list of four choices that detemine the player's base protection against damage sources.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Bullet Hit Power Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the amount of damage dealt by bullets from all weapons. Higher values means higher damage and faster kills.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Stamina Loss Factor: %c[ui_gray_2]Multiplier for the amount of stamina lost by movement/carry weight.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Max Carry Weight: %c[ui_gray_2]Controls the max amount of weight you can carry.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Enable Water Deprivation: %c[ui_gray_2]Activates thirst simulation, which means your character has to drink from time to time.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Enable Sleep Deprivation: %c[ui_gray_2]Allows the passage of time and use of consumables to gradually exhaust your character.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Enable Daytime Radiation: %c[ui_gray_2]Going outside during the day will expose your character to high, constant doses of radiation. A suitable outfit and helmet can provide you enough protection against the radioactive particles, as long as they are maintained properly.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Play Radiation Clicks (Geiger Only): %c[ui_gray_2]When enabled, radiation clicks can be heard only if you possess a Geiger Counter in your inventory with enough battery power.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Enable Anomaly Detector: %c[ui_gray_2]The default beeping sound that plays when a player approaches anomolous fields.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Gameplay difficulty factors are configured per current playthrough.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Gameplay difficulty factors are only accessible through loaded saves. You can tweak them inside the settings menu.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_disguise">
		<text>Disguise System</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_disguise_text">
		<text>You can %c[pda_white]disguise %c[ui_gray_2]yourself as a stalker from another faction to keep your true identity hidden for a variety of purposes.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]To disguise yourself as a member of a specific faction, you need to wear an appropriate outfit.\n \n
		While disguised, you can walk among faction members and act as one of them, even if they're hostile under normal circumstances. While in their presence, they will observe you and your behavior. A "suspiciousness" meter will appear on the HUD to indicate how suspicious you are in real time.\n \n
		Many factors play a role in the effectiveness of your disguise and affect the suspiciousness surrounding your character. Pay attention to the equipment you wear and its condition. Act normally and don't make any surprising moves to ensure that you don't draw unwanted attention.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Options\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can tweak the disguise factors through a variety of options inside the settings menu.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You cannot disguise yourself as a Monolith member, as they identify themselves through unknown means.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_fast_travel">
		<text>Fast Travel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_features_fast_travel_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Fast Travel &amp; Backpack Travel %c[ui_gray_2]allows you to travel to locations you have previously discovered by using your PDA's map.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Many locations are discovered as you travel, thus putting a marker on the map that allows you to click on it and fast travel.\n \n
		Backpack Travel functions the same, but depends on stashes that you've created.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Options\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can control fast travel and backpack travel through a variety of options inside the settings menu.\n \n
		%c[ui_red]ATTENTION\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You cannot fast travel if you're in combat, encumbered, heavily wounded, or during emissions.
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>