<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items">
		<text>Items</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_pda">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_pda_text">
		<text>A %c[pda_white]Personal Digital Assistant %c[ui_gray_2], or "%c[pda_white]PDA%c[ui_gray_2]", is a pocket-sized electronic device meant to encompass the basic and most vital functions of a computer.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The PDA is essential for daily information sharing. For this reason, almost every stalker in the Zone owns one.\n \n
		A GPS module is used to provide geolocation and time information to the user. Apart from basic functions, the PDA has many features, including access to the local network on which stalkers can easily communicate. The PDA also comes with an FM radio receiver, providing access to local radio channels.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Consumes %c[pda_white]0.1 mAh/s%c[ui_gray_2]. This consumption is higher for improved variants.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_upd">
		<text>UPD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_upd_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Universal Power Device %c[ui_gray_2]is a portable power unit about the size of a small walkie-talkie.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The UPD supplies electronic devices with power in an enhanced stream through a set of micro wires. These can be connected to any piece of equipment, regardless of its complexity or age, allowing stalkers to use and handle numerous electronic devices even if they have only one battery.\n \n
		All active devices will consume electric power from the UPD with consumption varying between devices. When the UPD runs out of charge, all connected devices will stop working.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]The UPD has a total power capacity of %c[pda_white]3Ah %c[ui_gray_2](ampere-hours).
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_basickit">
		<text>Basic Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_basickit_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Basic Tools %c[ui_gray_2]can be used for crafting basic equipment, devices and outfit upgrade parts.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Unlikely to be suitable for advanced maintenance, but could be useful in the hands of a thrifty technician. The kit contains different types and sizes of pliers, screws, adhesives and assorted fasteners.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Survival Guides %c[ui_gray_2]usually provide information on basic equipment and survival kits. With enough knowledge, a stalker can make great use out of this kit.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_advancedkit">
		<text>Advanced Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_advancedkit_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Advanced Tools %c[ui_gray_2]can be used for crafting better equipment, devices and outfit upgrade parts.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A decent set of tools, suitable for advanced maintenance. The kit contains a probe and pick set and a handful of small pliers and tipped tweezers.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Mechanic Manuals %c[ui_gray_2]provide information on mechanical engineering. With enough knowledge, a stalker can make great use out of this kit.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_expertkit">
		<text>Expert Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_expertkit_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Expert Tools %c[ui_gray_2]can be used for crafting high-quality equipment, devices and outfit upgrade parts.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A professional set of high quality tools for fine-tuning equipment. The kit contains a drill bit set, precision tweezers, soldiering iron, 4mm Screwdriver bits and a multimeter.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Engineering Manuals %c[ui_gray_2]provide information on industrial engineering. With enough knowledge, a stalker can make great use out of this kit.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_drugkit">
		<text>Drug-making Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_drugkit_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Drug-making Kit %c[ui_gray_2]can be used for crafting various types of drugs and medicines.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A kit containing some plastic packages, tablets and ampoules. People with enough knowledge on drugs can make use out of these kits. Keep an eye on those who possess %c[pda_white]Drug Recipes%c[ui_gray_2].
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_ammokit">
		<text>Gunsmithing Tools</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_itm_ammokit_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Gunsmithing Tools %c[ui_gray_2]can be used for recycling ammunition into other variants.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A decent set of gunsmithing tools and accessories, containing a pin punch set, wheeler hammer, press tool and a black powder measure kit.\n \n
		The %c[pda_white]Safety Guide to Ammunition %c[ui_gray_2]provides information on various types of ammunition, plus an in-depth view on the basic components of cartridges. With enough knowledge, a stalker can make great use out of this kit.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_kit_hunt">
		<text>Hunter's Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_kit_hunt_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Hunter's Kit %c[ui_gray_2]increases the number of body parts obtained from mutants when field-dressing.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A kit containing knives, a bag of hooks and other equipment used for skinning and gutting animals and mutants. Thanks to the variety of tools, the kit can also effectively improve weapon and armor maintenance.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_fieldcooker">
		<text>Gas Stove</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_fieldcooker_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Gas Stove %c[ui_gray_2]allows the ability to cook mutant meat.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The Gas Stove is extremely robust and reliable, was designed to handle demanding situations, extreme altitudes and both low and high temperatures and can be used with virtually any kind of fuel.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Details\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Mutant meats that do not require high temperature to be prepared are referred to as 'low-tier', whereas those that require high temperature are referred to as 'high-tier'.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Provides unlimited usage (as long as you have fuel).\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Can cook all types of meat.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Requires: %c[ui_gray_2]Jerry Can, Gas Balloon
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_cooking">
		<text>Field Cooking Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_cooking_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Field Cooking Kit %c[ui_gray_2]allows the ability to cook low-tier mutant meat.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A kit containing cooking accessories and utensils for use when camping and travelling, though it is unwieldy due to its heavy weight.\n \n
		Charcoal is available in the Zone at a relatively cheap price and is relatively light makings it perfect for longer trips in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Details\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Mutant meats that do not require high temperature to be prepared are referred to as 'low-tier', whereas those that require high temperature are referred to as 'high-tier'.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• Max Uses: %c[ui_gray_2]3\n
		%c[pda_white]• Requires: %c[ui_gray_2]Charcoal
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_army_bowler">
		<text>Army Kettle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_army_bowler_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Army Kettle %c[ui_gray_2]allows the ability to cook low-tier mutant meat.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A convinient kettle used for preparing and heating meals. The bowl cover can be used as a pan when heating or preparing a dish, with the handle of the lid designed to hold it. A tablespoon is also inserted into special holes on the handle.\n \n
		Charcoal is available in the Zone at a relatively cheap price and is relatively light makings it perfect for longer trips in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Details\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Mutant meats that do not require high temperature to be prepared are referred to as 'low-tier', whereas those that require high temperature are referred to as 'high-tier'.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• Max Uses: %c[ui_gray_2]7\n
		%c[pda_white]• Requires: %c[ui_gray_2]Charcoal or a Campfire
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_geiger">
		<text>Geiger Counter</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_geiger_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Geiger Counter %c[ui_gray_2] is used to measure radiation levels.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A Geiger counter measures ionizing (radioactive) radiation. Invented in 1908, Geiger Counters remain a popular technological device used for measurements in health, physics, industry, geology and other fields.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Usage\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The Geiger counter operates in 3 modes:
		%c[pda_white]• While Active: %c[ui_gray_2]displays the radiation level while the device is held\n
		%c[pda_white]• Always: %c[ui_gray_2]always displays the radiation level, as long as the device is in your inventory and its batteries are not drained.\n
		%c[pda_white]• On button click: %c[ui_gray_2]displays the radiation level on the press of a hotkey (see keybind options in the settings)\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Consumes %c[pda_white]0.1 mAh%c[ui_gray_2] per use.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_simple">
		<text>Echo Detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_simple_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Echo Detector %c[ui_gray_2]is a device with the ability to locate nearby artefacts.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This dated anomalous activity detector produces an alarm signal when anomalous particles enter a special chamber, allowing the device to register the presence of artefacts and measure the distance to the nearest one. The distance is indicated by the frequency of the sound the detector emits.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Can only locate the most common artefacts.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Consumes %c[pda_white]0.1 mAh/s%c[ui_gray_2].
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_advanced">
		<text>Bear detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_advanced_text">
		<text>
		The %c[pda_white]Bear Detector %c[ui_gray_2]is a device with the ability to locate nearby artefacts.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This last generation anomalous activity detector can be used to locate anomalous formations and has a color diode panel, which not only indicates the direction of artefacts, but also measures the distance to them. To switch to artefact search mode, open the device's front cover. Unfortunately, the device is programmed with a somewhat outdated list of detectable artefacts.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Can locate many kinds of artefacts, but not all.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Consumes %c[pda_white]0.15 mAh/s%c[ui_gray_2].		
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_elite">
		<text>Veles Detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_elite_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Veles Detector %c[ui_gray_2]is a device with the ability to locate nearby artefacts.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A next generation, scientific detector. Thanks to its three advanced detection chambers, the position of the artefact is displayed on a special LED screen in real-time. When closed, the device registers only the particles of anomalies and radiation.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Can locate many kinds of artefacts, but not all.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Consumes %c[pda_white]0.15 mAh/s%c[ui_gray_2].
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_scientific">
		<text>Svarog Detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_scientific_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Svarog Detector %c[ui_gray_2]is a device with the ability to locate nearby artefacts.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A prototype detector, with the expanded functionality of an anomalous frequency scanner. This device comes with a program that identifies any static areas of anomalous activity stored in the database, while retaining the ability to locate artefacts. The positions of both anomalous areas and artefacts are displayed on a special LED screen.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Able to detect all artefacts and even anomalous formations currently unknown to science.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Consumes %c[pda_white]0.2 mAh/s%c[ui_gray_2].
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_gps_tracker">
		<text>Military GPS Module</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_gps_tracker_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Military GPS Module %c[ui_gray_2]allows its user to locate nearby stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A prototype of the next generation GPS navigation devices with only a few copies being made. Although distributed exclusively among the highest military ranks, some devices have found their way into the hands of other parties as well. This improved module, featuring an improved framework and high sensitivity sensors, guarantees reliable operation even in the most hostile environments. Unlike usual GPS modules, this one relies on sets of codes that allows the module to acquire special privileges on the connected network. An automatic switching circuit inside the module, turns it off after 20 seconds of continuous scanning to save power.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Details\n
		%c[pda_white]• Scanning Time: %c[ui_gray_2]20 sec\n
		%c[pda_white]• Scanning Radius: %c[ui_gray_2]300 meters\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Consumes %c[pda_white]0.25 Ah%c[ui_gray_2] per use.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_lead_box">
		<text>LLMC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_lead_box_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Lead-lined Metal Container (LLMC) %c[ui_gray_2]is used to store artefacts while completely isolating their effects.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The LLMC is a simple metal box with thick walls and foam inserts as well as a heavy, pressure-sealing lid. Specifically designed for transporting artefacts within the Zone. Stops all radiation, thus ensuring user safety when in possession of artefacts. However, the device cannot be attached to the belt, stopping any positive or negative properties from being applied.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Details\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You must remove artefacts from the container prior to selling them.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Drag and drop an artefact on the container to store it inside.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Weight: %c[ui_gray_2]2.12kg
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_af_iam">
		<text>IAM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_af_iam_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Improvised Application Module (IAM) %c[ui_gray_2]is used to store artefacts and filter low radiation levels allowing its user to safely attach artefacts on their belt.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The IAM is the cheapest device that allows the user to harness the power of less potent artefacts by filtering a small amount of emitted radiation particles. Composed of multiple layers of lead, it is a low-cost alternative to the more reliable AAC and AAM. To attach to the belt, an artefact needs to be placed inside. The artefact will retain its characteristics with the exception of reduced radiation output. Due to its low quality, the IAM is only able to block beta particles.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Details\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You have to remove artefacts from the container prior to selling them.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Drag and drop an artefact on the container to store it inside.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Weight: %c[ui_gray_2]2.4 kg\n
		%c[pda_white]• Maximum Contained Radiation: %c[ui_gray_2]7 mSv
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_af_aac">
		<text>AAC</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_af_aac_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Artefact Application Container (AAC) %c[ui_gray_2]is used to store artefacts and filter moderate radiation levels, allowing its user to safely attach artefacts on their belt.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The AAC is the most cost-efficient device that allows the user to harness the power of more potent artefacts by filtering a moderate amount of emitted radiation particles. Composed of multiple layers of lead, with one layer of thorium, it is a good balance between the IAM and the AAM. To attach to the belt, an artefact needs to be placed inside. The artefact will retain its characteristics with the exception of reduced radiation output. Compared to the IAM, the AAC is capable of filtering out gamma rays.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Details\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You have to remove artefacts from the container prior to selling them.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Drag and drop an artefact on the container to store it inside.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Weight: %c[ui_gray_2]2.73kg\n
		%c[pda_white]• Maximum Contained Radiation: %c[ui_gray_2]12 mSv
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_af_aam">
		<text>AAM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_af_aam_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Artefact Application Module (AAM) %c[ui_gray_2]is used to store artefacts and filter dangerous radiation levels, allowing its user to safely attach artefacts on their belt.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The Artefact Application Module (AAM) filters a significant amount of radiation particles emitted from artefacts. This advanced mechanical module is the most effective way of harnessing the power of most potent artefacts. Artefact filter is composed of numerous layers made of nano-carbon. It is hence lightweight and has strongest radiation shielding properties of all devices. Regarded as a symbol of affluence in the Zone. Most commonly used by the scientists to minimise the harmful effects of artefacts. Designed and manufactured in Ukraine by a government institute which provides equipment for the scientists residing in the Zone of Alienation. In case of emergency or if no longer needed, the module can be utilised as a source of quality metal for use in outfit or helmet repairs. Currently unusable. To attach it to the belt, you have to put an artefact inside. The artefact will retain its characteristics with the exception of reduced radiation output. Compared to the AAC, the AAM is capable of filtering out neutrons. Formed by only the most unstable artefacts, neutrons are able to penetrate skin and, in high doses, damage DNA and internal organs by causing instability to a molecule's atomic nuclei, which may then in turn decay to cause further damage. Even if the neutron is 'safely' absorbed, sufficient exposure will lead to deuterium poisoning.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Details\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You have to remove artefacts from the container prior to selling them.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Drag and drop an artefact on the container to store it inside.\n
		%c[pda_white]• Weight: %c[ui_gray_2]3.06kg\n
		%c[pda_white]• Maximum Contained Radiation: %c[ui_gray_2]23 mSv\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_radio">
		<text>RF Receiver</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_items_detector_radio_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]RF Receiver %c[ui_gray_2]is a small device with a highly-sensitive RF module used for basic communications.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Quite common among soldiers despite the old technology. As the name suggests, it has the ability to interact with radio signals in a radius of 200m. The device is able to process radio waves with a frequency range between 30MHz and 300MHz.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Usage\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]While holding the receiver, you can switch the radio frequency.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Press the '%c[pda_white]Mouse-1%c[ui_gray_2]' button to increase the frequency.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Press the '%c[pda_white]Mouse-2%c[ui_gray_2]' button to decrease the frequency.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Hold the '%c[pda_white]Left-Shift%c[ui_gray_2]' button to increase frequency jumps by 10Hz while increasing / decreasing the current frequency.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Hold the '%c[pda_white]Left-Alt%c[ui_gray_2]' button to increase frequency jumps by 50Hz while increasing / decreasing the current frequency.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Consumes %c[pda_white]0.1 uAh/s%c.
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>