<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants">
		<text>Mutants</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_blind_dog">
		<text>Blind Dog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_blind_dog_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Blind Dogs %c[ui_gray_2]are the most familiar representative of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Several generations of the dog species have lived and died since the catastrophe. Each was more affected by the Zone than the previous. Rapid mutation lead to a vast improvement in previously peripheral abilities, frequently at the expense of primary ones. The most notable biological change was the loss of sight, paired with an uncanny development of smell. As it turned out, blind cubs survived in the Zone as well as normal ones, if not better. As a result, the common dog quickly became extinct in the Zone, giving way to a new breed. The animals instinctively identify and avoid anomalies, radiation and other invisible dangers that plague the Zone. Like their wild wolf ancestors, blind dogs hunt in packs. An encounter with a large group of these animals can be dangerous even to an experienced and well-armed stalker.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Low\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_bloodsucker">
		<text>Bloodsucker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_bloodsucker_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Bloodsuckers %c[ui_gray_2],as the name would suggest, are hematophagous monsters.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Experienced stalkers describe this semi-legendary beast as a tall, hunched humanoid with a mess of tentacles where its mouth should be. According to those who saw it and lived to tell the tale, the creature uses its tentacles to cling to the victim's throat, paralyze it, and suck it dry of blood with a mummified shell is all that's left of what used to be a living human being. However, the most astounding feature of the Bloodsucker is its ability to become invisible. Countless dead or missing stalkers are said to have perished in the merciless grip of a Bloodsucker. The lucky few who have survived an encounter tell spine-chilling tales of marshes and subterranean areas haunted by the Zone's version of Count Dracula.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Camouflage, Blood-sucking\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]A rare subspecies once existed in the Great Swamp which carried its victims away, never to be seen again.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_boar">
		<text>Boar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_boar_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Boars %c[ui_gray_2]are a common mutant found in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A massive, mutated animal, reaching 1.5 meters at the shoulder. The Zone boar's aggressiveness and ability to survive by far surpass those of its relatives outside the contaminated area. Radiation and anomalies left their mark on the physical appearance of the animal as its fur is entirely gone in some places and long and bristly in others. The hooves have evolved into sturdy, sharp claws, while the pupils have became colorless with its bald head marred by pigmentation Known to usually charge at their victims, trying to knock them over and then rip them to shreds.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Slow\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_burer">
		<text>Burer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_burer_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Burers %c[ui_gray_2]are stocky, almost dwarf-like monsters that usually stick to underground areas.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]These ugly yellowish pygmies are another mutant of possible human origin and an example of how the Zone is capable of altering the DNA of all living organisms, twisting them into nightmarish creations. These mutants inhabit underground tunnels and catacombs, as their sensitive eyes are too sensitive to daylight. They've been known to set up elaborate ambushes which strike any stalkers or science teams that delve into their shelter. Their usual tactic is to lie in wait as prey enters their area, after which they will quietly block all exits with large pieces of garbage, debris and concrete fractions thanks to their telekinetic abilities. Killed victims are torn to pieces by the dwarves' strong hands and then devoured. Interactions with other mutants are mostly peaceful, although blind dogs attack them without mercy. Burers posses a genuine intellect, and their vile character and nervous spite lead them to sometimes perform unexpected and savage deeds. Burers seem to telepathically sense nearby life forms and are able to determine their disposition without any visual contact. For this reason it is impossible to get in close proximity with a Burer without them already being aware of your presence. Their telekinesis allows them to distantly manipulate large objects, hurling them at their opponents at high speeds. They can also inflict powerful telekinetic blows directly on the victim and are even able to create telekinetic shields to stop bullets or pull a stalker's weapon from their hands. Burers are some of the the most dangerous mutants in the dark areas of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee, Psychic\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Slow\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Psy-powers, Telekinesis\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Some Burers are excellent mimics, able to imitate sounds such as bird cries, dog barks, human laughter or even a crying infant.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Burers often focus on defeating their opponents by wearing them down. Heavily armed and armored stalkers tend to suffer most when fighting against them.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]A Burer's diet tends to consist of kimchi and human flesh.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_cat">
		<text>Cat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_cat_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Cats %c[ui_gray_2]in the Zone are heavily mutated local wildcats.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Much like many of the Zone's dogs, these mutants are remnants of regular house cats which were unfortunate enough to have survived the second disaster and replicated in the Zone long enough to become terribly mutated. Unlike dogs, which attack in packs, cats for the most part remain solitary and will hunt as single individuals. They are extremely stealthy and their claws and teeth have become elongated and exceptionally sharp. They are very aggressive and will now actively hunt humans as potential prey. Unlike dogs, which directly attack stalkers in large groups, a single cat will very quietly stalk its prey and attack from behind without making a sound. For this reason, it is arguable that a single Zone cat may be more dangerous than a pack of dogs. A popular campfire rumor states that some veteran stalkers have been lured by voices of others pleading for help from within deep foliage, only to be attacked by a cat leaping out of the shrubbery. So far, any proof for these cats being able to imitate human voices remains unproven.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Low\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Cats are a surprisingly frequent cause of death amongst new stalkers as they often strike before its victim is aware of its presence.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_chimera">
		<text>Chimera</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_chimera_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Chimeras %c[ui_gray_2]are hairless monsters, close to the size of an adult lion.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The result of horrible genetic mutation on an unidentified organism? Perhaps a victim of cruel experimentation? The origin of this beast remains unknown. Adult specimens can reach up to 1.4 meters in length. A highly intelligent, strong and swift beast whose attacks and predatory habits resemble that of a tiger. Prefers to remain in concealment and strike victims from the back without a single sound. Doubled essential organs and vital systems lead to extreme levels of endurance with the beast able to survive wounds normally fatal otherwise. This is additionally amplified by extraordinary regenerative abilities. Their only worthy natural opponents in the Zone are Chernobyl dogs and Pseudogiants.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] High\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Nimble, Regenerative\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]While fairly resistant to bullets, Chimeras are notably vulnerable towards chemical and thermal anomalies.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]While generally solitary creatures, it is not unheard of for Chimeras to hunt in pairs.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Two especially powerful Chimeras kept Zaton and Yanov in terror during 2012. Both were eventually hunted down and killed by a stalker named Alexander.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_controller">
		<text>Controller</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_controller_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Controllers %c[ui_gray_2]are some of the most dangerous psychic mutants in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A rare humanoid mutant more commonly seen near the center of the Zone. Bears a superficial resemblance to a human with a disproportionately large head and diseased looking skin. Possesses a good level of intelligence and perception and has the ability to control the behavior of less developed creatures. Mature specimens are reportedly capable of taking control over the human mind. This may lead to the destruction of higher cognition, reducing the victim into a vegetative or zombified state or in more complex cases, may influence the victim to commit suicide. This is a ferocious enemy and even the most experienced stalkers are afraid of meeting it. Veterans warn that Controllers prefer to lay in wait and allow you to approach before striking though it is possible to sense the telepathic probing of a Controller if it is nearby, giving advanced warning of its presence.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee, Psychic\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Slow\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Passive Damage, Psi-powers, Mind Control
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_crow">
		<text>Crow</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_crow_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Crow%c[ui_gray_2] is one of the few bird species to have survived in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The only bird species to have survived in the Zone, enduring increased radiation levels and effectively avoiding anomalies. While the army pilots need to rely on complex detectors to avoid gravitational disturbances, the crow seems to rely on its own senses; a mystery that drives ornithologists and biologists mad. Various theories attempting to explain the phenomenon exist, with all of them pointing to a highly specialized development of the brain.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] None\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Low\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_flesh">
		<text>Flesh</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_flesh_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Flesh %c[ui_gray_2]are heavily mutated pigs.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Like most other living creatures in the Zone, the domestic pig also underwent serious biological changes since the day of the catastrophe. It seems the genes responsible for metabolism were especially affected in this case. Mutant pigs, known simply as "Flesh" among the stalkers, are one of the most vivid examples of the Zone's disastrous perversion of nature. Mutant pigs developed a protective layer of scales and exoskeletal plates. Their regeneration potential increased several times, as did the complexity of their nervous system. Just like a normal pig, a Flesh is an omnivore and may attack a stalker if hungry.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Slow\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_fracture">
		<text>Fracture</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_fracture_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Fractures %c[ui_gray_2]are former, seemingly devolved humans with an animalistic mindset.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Either a result of unknown mutations during some artificial experiment or the outcome of the Zone's influence on human survivors. Strongly marked hypertrophy of the extremities. Expresses slight psi-abilities. Humanoid outward appearance and the manner to stoop and hide its hand under a cloak give the mutant a look of a vagrant. The creature is artful at attracting stalkers by starting a conversation or asking a question. When the victim turns its back, the mutant stands up and attacks by means of its powerful extremity. Has been seen to feed on rats, blind dogs and fleshes. Rare cases have them chasing lonely stalkers, attacking them in the night.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Slow\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Sometimes a Fracture will call for help when spotting stalkers. It is unknown whether they're calling to their fellow mutants or to the stalkers.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_karlik">
		<text>Karlik</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_karlik_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Karliks %c[ui_gray_2]are very rare dwarf-like mutants which hide away in seclusion.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]It is unclear whether or not they are related to Burers, but they share a great many psychic similarities making it difficult to dismiss this as just coincidence. On the few rare occasions that observations have been made, Karliks are seen captivated by certain locations or artefacts, as if they have tasked themselves with the responsibility of protecting them, proceeding to attack anything that comes too close. Hardly anything else is known about them, as most who have encountered the creatures are often found dead or crazy with no discernible physical injuries.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee, Psychic\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Slow\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Passive Damage, Phantom Projection, Psy-powers, Telekinesis\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]While often compared to the Burer, the Karlik focuses more on illusions and telepathy than telekinesis.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]If one accepts that Karliks and Burers were lab creations, the former was likely an earlier iteration of the latter.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_lurker">
		<text>Lurker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_lurker_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Lurker %c[ui_gray_2]is a hybrid mutant with great physical power.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Rumors say that Lurkers were a part of an experiment that occurred in one of the hidden labs around the Zone before the second disaster. Yet, the first wave of Lurkers were spotted in 2013, near the outskirts of Pripyat. Their strong multi-layered skin, abnormal muscular endurance and sense of hearing has gained the Lurkers the ability to survive in the worst environment conditions. Their hind legs allows them to jump huge distances and strike their victims. Local hunters are known to collect the creature's eyes for their unique yellow glow.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_poltergeist">
		<text>Poltergeist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_poltergeist_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Poltergeists %c[ui_gray_2]are strange, almost invisible creatures haunting the deeper reaches of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Supernatural in the eyes of some, these are invisible creatures that haunt the deeper reaches of the Zone, usually old, abandoned buildings. Nothing is known about their origin, although rumors in circulation claim they are spirits of stalkers hit by a massive wave of radiation. Their mysterious appearances and disappearances seem to correspond to the poltergeist legend, hence the name. Known encounters with poltergeists are quite diverse, from mischievous laughter and blood-chilling howling, to deadly fireballs appearing out of nowhere. Unfortunately, all information about the poltergeist phenomenon originates from unclear and contradictory stories of questionable validity.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Psychic\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Psy-powers, Telekinesis\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Older stalkers report Poltergeists occasionally leaving a body behind. Younger stalkers don't tend to believe them.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudodog">
		<text>Pseudodog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudodog_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Pseudodogs %c[ui_gray_2]are relatively common canine mutants.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Despite the name, the Pseudodogs evolved directly from wolves. The animals inhabiting the forests at the time of the catastrophe gave rise to one of the Zone's most dangerous mutant species. Pseudodogs are about as different from mutant dogs as wild wolves differ from poodles. The creatures mark and guard their territory carefully, attacking anyone or anything stupid enough to venture onto their land. Lightning-fast reflexes, uncanny dexterity and razor-sharp teeth make the Pseudodog a formidable enemy for even large mutants and well-armed stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Nimble
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogeist">
		<text>Pseudogeist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogeist_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Pseudogeists %c[ui_gray_2]are a rare cloud-like subspecies of Poltergeists.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Very little is known about these creatures, as their appearance within the Zone is a recent occurrence. Appearing as a pulsating, burgundy-colored series of clouds, they will attempt to kill anything unfortunate enough to wander into them. There are no specific locations where they are found as they tend to appear in the most unsuspecting of places.\n \n
		Upon death they explode into multiple cloud-like formations before dissipating.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Psychic\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Psy-powers\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogiant">
		<text>Pseudogiant</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pseudogiant_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Pseudogiants %c[ui_gray_2]are one of the rarest and most fearsome mutants in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The Pseudogiant resembles a massive, drop-shaped abdomen with a pair of disproportionately large limbs which function as arms and legs simultaneously. The creature uses these appendages to move around and grab its victims. An adult Pseudogiant can weigh up to two tons and stand 2 meters tall. Their clumsy appearance might be deceiving, since they can move very rapidly if needed. Their muscles are exceptionally powerful and their bones are as hard as steel. The creature's brain is protected by a sturdy (up to 10 centimeters thick) skull, while many complex functions are controlled by the spinal medulla. Another astonishing feature of the beast is its ability to create local shock waves, which damage all living things in the vicinity.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Very high\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Slow\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Immense Strength\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Curiously, most Pseudogiants, while territorial, are among the least aggressive of the Zone's mutants. However, to the average stalker, that really isn't saying much.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_psydog">
		<text>Psy-dog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_psydog_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Psy-dogs %c[ui_gray_2]are a rare subspecies of Pseudodogs, possessing unique psychic abilities.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The most distinguishing feature of the Psy-dog is its ability to affect the minds of others, where it is able to create seemingly live images of itself. These are different from regular phantoms produced by psy-fields and some other mutants, as they look more real and solid and can, at least to the mind, hurt what they attack. Visually, they are almost indistinguishable from Pseudodogs aside from having large streaks of grey/white fur.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee, Psychic\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Nimble, Phantom Projection
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_psysucker">
		<text>Psysucker</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_psysucker_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Psysuckers %c[ui_gray_2]are the relative species of Bloodsuckers that possess unique psychic abilities.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Origins unknown, Psysuckers are one of the most mysterious creatures in the Zone. Autopsy results show a lot of similarities to the Bloodsuckers, especially with the optic camouflage which allows them to temporarily become almost invisible to the naked eye. On the contrary, further studies has shown that Psysuckers hold a developed nervous system unlike their relatives, which points towards their unique ability to affect the minds of others, where it's able to create seemingly live images of itself. A notable difference is that Psysuckers lack the tentacles protruding from a Blooduscker's face.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee, Psychic\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Low\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Camouflage, Phantom Projection\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pyrogeist">
		<text>Pyrogeist</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_pyrogeist_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Pyrogeists %c[ui_gray_2]are a rare pyrokinetic subspecies of Poltergeists.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Appearing as a floating form of heat haze surrounded by a fiery glow, they are easily distinguishable from regular Poltergeists. On death, they explode in a mess of blood and fire. Their primary and only attack is spawning pillars of flame, similar to burner anomalies, which it uses to try to burn its enemies to death as it lacks any telekinetic abilities.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Psychic (Thermal)\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Psy-powers
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_rat">
		<text>Rat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_rat_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Rats %c[ui_gray_2]are small, hungry rodents found in and around deserted buildings.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]After people abandoned the exclusion Zone during the first incident, rats flourished in number and continue to thrive in the Zone. They are expert survivors and instinctively avoid anomalies and emissions. Their main habitats are sewage headers, tunnels and basements. These animals seldom leave the underground, and will aggressively attack in swarms if threatened. The Zone did not influence their phenotype, although they now posses an increased resistance to mutation sustained from ionizing radiation.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Low\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• Easily the most harmless mutant in the Zone, they're generally hunted for their meat, rather than the danger they pose.
		%c[pda_white]• Rats are the less aggressive and less obviously mutated cousin of the Tushkano.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_snork">
		<text>Snork</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_snork_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Snorks %c[ui_gray_2]are horrifically mutated soldiers and stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]It seems these creatures were human at some point, though it is difficult to imagine what conditions could turn a human being into such a disgusting beast. Snorks are insane creatures leading a beast's life and differing little from other carnivorous monsters in the Zone. They move on all fours in long jumps, constantly sniffing the ground in hope of picking up the scent of prey. They hunt carefully, in a calculated manner, frequently setting up ambushes. Thanks to its uncanny reflexes and powerful muscles, the Snork can approach a victim, pin it down in one long, accurate jump and then tear it to shreds in a matter of seconds. Strips of army uniforms and other clothing are occasionally found on their bodies so it stands to reason that they are all that's left of missing military stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] Nimble\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• Originally thought to be unfortunate survivors of the very first military expeditions into the Zone, their continued presence into 2018 has opened up dark avenues of thought and speculation regarding their true nature.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_tushkano">
		<text>Tushkano</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_tushkano_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Tushkanos %c[ui_gray_2]are small rat-like creatures which move about on their two hind legs.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Although they bear a striking resemblance to jerboas, there is actually no link between the two. Attempts at determining the exact species from which this rodent evolved have so far been unsuccessful, although its ancestor must have been a gregarious rodent. Reaching up to 40cm at the shoulder, the animal is far more dexterous, aggressive and ravenous than its desert cousin. Mutant rodents live mainly in basements of destroyed buildings, feeding on everything they can get their teeth into, from plants to careless stalkers. Occasionally a pack of rodents will attack and kill large animals and mutants, tearing them apart before they can escape.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Low\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_zombie">
		<text>Zombie</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_mutants_zombie_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Zombies %c[ui_gray_2]are stalkers who have been reduced to their most residual reflexes.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The Brain Scorcher strips its victim of mind and reason, leaving only an empty shell. The brainless bodies then turn into zombies, following only the most basic instincts, wandering aimlessly around the Zone without weapons or clothing. Zombies are little more than sluggish walking corpses, caring only about food and sleep. They eat and drink just about anything they can get their claws on, thus they are virtually soaked in radiation and toxic waste. Usually they roam the Zone without any apparent purpose or just lie corpse-like in abandoned buildings. However, as soon as they sense the presence, they attack immediately and some are even capable of using firearms to a very limited ability. Experienced stalkers have learned to avoid them and preserve ammo.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks:%c[ui_gray_2] Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health:%c[ui_gray_2] Low\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed:%c[ui_gray_2] Slow\n
		%c[pda_white]• Unique Traits:%c[ui_gray_2] None\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• A true tragedy, it is best to put these poor souls out of their misery.
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>