<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic">
		<text>Historic</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_final_day">
		<text>Final Day</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_final_day_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Final Day %c[ui_gray_2]were a faction of scientists, also known as %c[pda_green]Last Day%c[ui_gray_2], or as "%c[pda_green]wild stalkers%c[ui_gray_2]".\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]They believed that the Zone would ultimately bring about the end of the world, expanding into and claiming ever more land with each passing emission. Aside from their fascination with hunting zombified stalkers for research purposes, and that their now-forgotten leader was assassinated by a stalker called Ghost, little else is known about them.\n \n
		With their activity occurring shortly after the emission that wiped out much of Clear Sky, it is possible they were a small splinter group; survivors who became unhinged from what they had witnessed.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Leaders: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		%c[pda_white]• Headquarters: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		%c[pda_white]• Colors: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]All that is known about this faction is from game design documents.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This faction was cut from %c[pda_white]S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Shadow of Chernobyl%c[ui_gray_2].
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_isg">
		<text>ISG</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_isg_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]International Scientific Group %c[ui_gray_2]was founded to research the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Following the sudden appearance of the Zone, the United Nations created a new research body with its sole purpose being to research and explain this strange new phenomenon.\n
		An area far in the north surrounding six large generators was seen as the most scientifically interesting, and as such was picked as the site for their expedition. Lasting only a few months, their work was plagued by problems they could never have known to prepare for. Researchers would be consumed by unseen anomalies, or ravaged by the horrifically mutated wildlife. Others would inexplicably disappear, only to return days later in a zombified trance trying to kill their colleagues.\n \n
		The expedition was eventually shut down after accomplishing very little, and resulting in an unacceptably high body count. Undeterred by their failure, an institute was created by the Ukrainian government to carry on their work, now commonly referred to as the Ecologists.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Leaders: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		%c[pda_white]• Headquarters: %c[ui_gray_2]Generators\n
		%c[pda_white]• Colors: %c[ui_gray_2]White &amp; Red\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia%c[ui_gray_2]\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This faction was cut from %c[pda_white]S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky%c[ui_gray_2].
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_renegade">
		<text>Renegade</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_renegade_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Renegades %c[ui_gray_2]were some of the most despicable stalkers in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Having no limits or morals, they consisted mainly of stalkers who had committed crimes so terrible that their original factions had cast them out. The only law they respected was one of force, preying on the weak at the perimeters of the Zone, often those who were too young and inexperienced to stand any chance against them.\n \n
		Driven into the marshes by their numerous enemies, it was only in the face of Clear Sky that their desire to survive forced these jackals to unite as a faction of their own.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Leaders: %c[ui_gray_2]Unknown\n
		%c[pda_white]• Headquarters: %c[ui_gray_2]Great Swamp\n
		%c[pda_white]• Colors: %c[ui_gray_2]Various\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia%c[ui_gray_2]\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]They appeared very briefly in %c[pda_white]S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Clear Sky%c[ui_gray_2].\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This faction only existed so the player could befriend bandits.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_rat_wolf">
		<text>Rat Wolf</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_rat_wolf_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Rat Wolf %c[ui_gray_2]was a rare subspecies of mutated rats.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Much more dangerous than their existing cousins currently found in the Zone, the rat wolf was an indiscriminate killing machine. Often leading packs of regular rats, these creatures were easy to spot in comparison as they frequently grew to be about two or three times as large.\n \n
		Aside from this there were only a few differences in their appearance, such as having larger, entirely black eyeballs, with swollen and fat upper bodies. Natural selection eventually played its part, as due to their unnatural size they often stood out and were easy pickings for the Zone's cats and other similar mutants.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks: %c[ui_gray_2]Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health: %c[ui_gray_2]Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed: %c[ui_gray_2]Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Traits: %c[ui_gray_2]None\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia%c[ui_gray_2]\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]All that is known about this mutant is from game design documents.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This mutant was cut from %c[pda_white]S.T.A.L.K.E.R.: Shadow of Chernobyl%c[ui_gray_2].
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_tark">
		<text>Tark</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_historic_tark_text">
		<text>The %c[pda_white]Tark %c[ui_gray_2]was an extinct horse-like creature, likely mutated from the Przewalski's horse.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This creature bore little resemblance to its ancestors due to massive exposure to radiation upon the Zone's inception. Its hind legs were atrophied whereas those at its anterior had become visibly exaggerated, whilst its tail and much of its mouth had all but decayed or disappeared.\n \n
		Similar in ways to a Flesh, the Tark's body was greatly swollen and bloated. They were also frequently seen hunting in large groups, though probably as more of an instinctual relic than any natural form of a herd.\n \n
		Unlike other mutants in the Zone, they were incredibly feral animals, with their madness often overwhelming their perception of fear and likely contributing to their eventual downfall.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Statistics\n
		%c[pda_white]• Attacks: %c[ui_gray_2]Melee\n
		%c[pda_white]• Health: %c[ui_gray_2]Average\n
		%c[pda_white]• Speed: %c[ui_gray_2]Fast\n
		%c[pda_white]• Traits: %c[ui_gray_2]Frenzied\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Trivia%c[ui_gray_2]\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]All that is known about this mutant is from what accompanied its submission.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This mutant lost to the Snork in the Monster Ball competition by GSC Game World.
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>