<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>

	<string id="encyclopedia_gamma">
		<text>G.A.M.M.A. Manual</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_gamma_text">
		<text>%c[pda_green]G.A.M.M.A. %c[pda_white]Manual</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_aaintro">
		<text>--- Welcome to G.A.M.M.A. ---</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_aaintro_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Welcome to %c[pda_green]G.A.M.M.A\n \n
		%c[pda_green]G.A.M.M.A. %c[ui_gray_2]stands for Grok's Automated Modular Modpack for Anomaly. This modpack also features its own new modular set of add-ons including:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]A new UI.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]A rebalanced survival experience focused on crafting, repairing and cooking.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]A sense of progression during your playthrough thanks to small and global changes of most systems and gameplay loops.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Rebalanced damage system for the player and NPCs.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Rebalanced gun ballistics and melee system damage.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Overhauled radiation effects and dynamic radiation areas.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Many fixes for some major addons including the Boomsticks and Sharpsticks gun pack.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]A new economy where traders will only sell you supplies, and where good ammunition will only be available to trustful stalkers.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]New starting loadouts focused on providing pistols, SMGs or WW2 guns to have a smoother start with calibers for which you can buy ammo. Also provided to you are the basic tools to wander the Zone, which is nice for Ironman runs.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]And so much more!
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_progress">
		<text>Progression</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_progress_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]How To Progress\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A. progression are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Perform tasks, kill mutants, collect their parts, keep these parts to complete stalker collection tasks.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Collect stash coordinates, visit those stashes (%c[pda_white]white %c[ui_gray_2]or %c[pda_green]green %c[ui_gray_2]icons on the PDA map), to get nice loot and toolkits.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Use the acquired toolkits to craft repair kits for guns and armor you found to improve your gear and chance of survival.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]By completing tasks you will earn goodwill for different factions to buy better supplies, including better ammo for your shiny new guns.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_healing">
		<text>Healing &amp; Medicine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_healing_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Healing and Medicine\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A. healing are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Use basic healing items like medkits or bandages to heal your main health; this heals your limbs temporarily (%c[pda_yellow]yellow %c[ui_gray_2]HP).\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]To convert the temporary HP (%c[pda_yellow]yellow%c[ui_gray_2]) to permanent HP (%c[pda_white]white%c[ui_gray_2]) for your limbs, use post-heal items such as Ibuprofen, Fentanyl, Antidote or Yadulin.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Any medicine with %c[pda_white]white %c[ui_gray_2]dots in their description will heal temporary HP for that limb or area. Such healing items have a %c[pda_white]white %c[ui_gray_2]heart icon.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Post-healing will give you side effects such as extreme hunger or dizziness. Dizziness can be cured using stamina boosting medicine or water.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Keep in mind that damage resistance injectors work (indicated by a shield icon).\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You don't need every medical item to heal your body. Mark the most important ones as a favorite for easy access.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_crafting">
		<text>Crafting</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_crafting_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Crafting\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A. crafting are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Crafting is based on toolkits that you will find in marked stashes.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Right-click any toolkit to open a portable workbench to start crafting, repairing or upgrading your gear.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]There are 6 types of toolkits: Basic, Advanced, Expert, Medical, Gunsmith and the Artefact Melter.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Almost all recipes are available from the start, including cooking recipes.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Some recipes are locked. These are mainly advanced exos PSU recipes. You can get these from Lv5 supply Mercenary and Ecologist traders.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]"Junk" items that are necessary for crafting recipes are indicated by a hammer and pincer icon. Keep these.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Disassembling the gear you find will allow you to retrieve crafting parts. Some of these items are valuable, so be sure to keep those if you need extra cash.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_cooking">
		<text>Cooking</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_cooking_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Cooking\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A. cooking are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]All cooking recipes are available from the start.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Cooking is essential as it will provide high calorie food for cheap.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Using the basic cooking kit near bonfires will allow you to cook without the need of charcoal.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]The advanced cooking kit requires liquid fuel to work. However, it is able to cook high tier meals which provide useful long-lasting buffs.	
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_radiation">
		<text>Radiation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_radiation_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Radiation\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]GAMMA features dynamic radiation and a revamped radiation damage system. The basics of G.A.M.M.A. radiation are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]New random radiation patches are spawned when starting a new game.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Radiation will slowly reduce your health (much slower than Vanilla) and will reduce your max stamina.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]The more irradiated you are, the more likely critical organs will be damaged. This results in the player character coughing and losing a significant amount of health.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]The radiation meter can be found at the bottom left corner of the screen. If it starts being filled, you just hit a radiation patch. Try to backtrack to avoid traversing it. Radiation can also come from artefacts that are not in a container.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Use anti-rad drugs, cigarettes, tobacco, water, or alcohol to cure radiation. Using rad protecting/resistance drugs is also a good way to avoid radiation.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]The more to the North you go, the more dangerous the radiation will be. Be sure to have a good gas mask before going into the northern areas. Entering the Army Warehouses or areas further North without a gas mask or proper anti-radiation medication can be fatal if you hit just one bad radiation patch. Keep in mind that running into an area with strong radiation will likely make you unable to move, exhausting you and sealing your fate...
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_stashes">
		<text>Stashes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_stashes_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Stashes\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A. stashes are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Stashes are the main source of toolkits, which are the most critical items you need to progress.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Unmarked stashes are almost always empty.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Stashes must be marked to contain anything of value, especially toolkits.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Stash content is tied to the map they spawn in.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]The more to the North a stash is in the Zone, the better the loot.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Expert toolkits can only be found in the Red Forest or further North.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Storing stuff in stashes is safe: it won't be looted by NPCs.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Even if the stash is marked at some point, content will spawn in the stash on top of what you previously stored. 
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_disguise">
		<text>Disguise</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_disguise_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Disguise\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of the G.A.M.M.A. disguise system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can wear other faction's armor and be considered a member of that faction if the faction’s patch is attached.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]If you tear off the patch, you'll be considered as a member of your characters faction.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]When attaching the patch, you need to be out of the field of view of other stalkers, so your disguise doesn't get blown.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This feature is especially powerful with ecologist armor, but they are very hard to get your hands on in GAMMA.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]The condition of the armor impacts how easy you will be spotted.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]High ranking stalkers will see through your tricks more easily than those of lower rank.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_inventory">
		<text>Inventory</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_inventory_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Inventory\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of the G.A.M.M.A. inventory system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Inventory management is easy; just clean your inventory from unnecessary mess by storing items in a stash of choice.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Holding %c[pda_white]Shift %c[ui_gray_2]while moving your cursor in your inventory will transfer the entire stack of items you are currently hovering over. Pressing %c[pda_white]Shift+T %c[ui_gray_2]performs a "%c[pda_white]Take All%c[ui_gray_2]".\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Water bottles are better weight-wise than canteens to quench thirst. Keep the canteens in your main stash to cook with.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Mutant parts and meat do not weight much. Keeping some in your inventory will allow you to complete tasks.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Crafting tools don't weight much, and you can %c[pda_white]right-click %c[ui_gray_2]them to "%c[pda_white]open workbench%c[ui_gray_2]" and start crafting on-the-go.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ammunition can be quite heavy, but disassembled ammo parts are very lightweight. Keep these parts and craft ammo with your gunsmith toolkit on-the-go. Be sure to disassemble all unnecessary ammo.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can %c[pda_white]right-click %c[ui_gray_2]and mark some items as "%c[pda_white]Favorite%c[ui_gray_2]" and others as "%c[pda_white]Junk%c[ui_gray_2]". This will give you easy access to the important items that will always be on the top of every inventory container. This is the opposite for junk, which will always be at the bottom.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_lore">
		<text>Lore</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_lore_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Lore\n \n
		After the fall of the Monolith, thanks to Strelok, the Zone became a place of science and discoveries. The zone wasn't a secret place anymore and the UN began to ban the sale of firearms in the Zone to make it more peaceful, with paid PMCs ensuring the security of scientists and limiting fights between factions. Indeed, the EU and UN decided to put a stop to the bloodshed in the Zone as well as gun smuggling from the Zone to nearby countries by limiting gun traffic. No faction wanted to give the UN and EU any more reasons to contract more private military companies. PMCs were already crawling throughout the Zone.\n \n
		During that period of peace, new discoveries were made, such as artefact melting, fusion, and empowering thanks to the work of Prof. Sakharov. This "Golden Age" of science in the Zone however made the existing factions weaker since the Monolith was not a priority anymore. Deep in the heart of the Zone and CNPP, the Monolith were secretly getting stronger, and a new group of fanatics began to emerge, even crazier than the Monolith if the rumors were to be believed.\n \n
		Fast forward to 2018, the Golden Age of the Zone is over, and the Monolith have returned and reactivated the miracle machine and the brain scorcher. It's 2012 all over again. The weakened factions have grown even weaker; no longer the hardened Monolith killers they were back in the old days. The only hope of most stalkers? Finding Strelok. Some say he's still alive, and Doc, one of his old friends, might have some leads regarding to his location.\n \n
		You arrive in the Zone in the middle of this mess. You are tasked with finding Strelok and helping clean the Zone from the Monolith scourge.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_money">
		<text>Money</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_money_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Money\n \n
		%c[pda_white]In GAMMA money is of the essence, especially in the beginning. The basics are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]There are fast ways to make cash, namely doing tasks without picking fights, such as selling artefacts or selling mutant parts to the ecologists.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You'll find yourself often spending money on healing items, but this is intended. The more you play, the better the toolkits you'll have and the easier it will be to repair good gear and craft items. This will, of course, save money and make fights easier, thus helping you to save even more money.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]During the mid-game, you'll inevitably get loads of money. This can be used to upgrade your equipment or invest in expensive AP ammo.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can also buy detectors and NVGs at traders or craft them and save some money. Maintaining an exoskeleton suit will also be a money sink since you often need to buy expensive exo batteries.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Better healing items are also a must to have easier fights as using stimpaks will greatly help you in tense situations.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_plates">
		<text>Protection Plates</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_plates_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Protection Plates\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Armor Plate belt attachments are on par with artefact protection, reaching about 15% ballistic and explosive, respectively.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Basic Kevlar armor plates are obtained via questlines (basic tier 1 plate) or crafted from using armor parts.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Armor plates can be upgraded via the crafting system:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Tier 1 can be upgraded to tier 2 with lots of armor parts.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Tier 2 Kevlar can be upgraded to tier 3 with lots of armor parts.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Tier 3 can be upgraded to tier 4 with lots of armor parts.\n \n
		This system should push the player to scavenge armor parts for longer.\n
		Armor parts used in this system are conveniently marked with a hammer and pincer icon for easy sorting and looting. This should prevent players that don't want to engage in artefacts hunting to not die miserably once they fight monolith and sin in the North, which are exclusively using AP ammo.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_arty">
		<text>Artefact Reinvention</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_arty_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Artefact Reinvention\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A.'s artefact system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]The new Grizzly Detector is used to find all artefacts, even with NVGs on and is craftable with an advanced toolkit.\n
		%c[pda_white]• New Artefact Spawning System: %c[ui_gray_2]Artefacts spawn randomly within anomalous fields in the player's current map so be sure to check them whenever you can!\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Rare artefacts also respawn in the labs after emissions.\n
		%c[pda_white]• New Artefact Quality System: %c[ui_gray_2]Artefacts spawn with a random low condition (or "quality") to mimic that every artefact is different. With the new Artefacts Melter, you can combine artefacts to make them stronger and increase their quality.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Artefacts Melter:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Buy it at Sakharov or Herman for about 30k RU.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can craft stronger artefacts (%c[pda_white]right-click > fuse artefacts%c[ui_gray_2]) or empower them (%c[pda_white]right-click > empower artefacts%c[ui_gray_2]).\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Every action you take with the Artefact Melter will consume charges.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can refill the Artefact Melter by holding %c[pda_white]Left-Alt %c[ui_gray_2]and dragging it on top of any artefact.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Keeping an empty melter on you is a good way to replenish it on your way through the zone with unwanted artefacts.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Artefact Empowering:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Combine two exactly similar artefacts to sum up their condition / quality.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can combine any junk artefact with any other junk artefact at a reduced rate.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Artefact Crafting:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Access the craft menu as usual. There will be a new crafting subsection: Artefacts.\n 
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This will allow you to convert multiple artefacts of a given tier to the tier above:\n
		%c[pda_white]• Junk > Tier 1 (7mS).\n
		%c[pda_white]• Tier 1 > Tier 2 (12mS).\n
		%c[pda_white]• Tier 2 > Tier 3 (23mS).\n
		%c[pda_white]• Tier 3 > Special.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_energy">
		<text>Energy Management</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_energy_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Energy Management\n \n
		%c[pda_white] Energy in GAMMA is a balancing act between travel, food, drinks, medicine and sleep. The basics of G.A.M.M.A.'s energy system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You character will be tired at the end of the day. You must sleep to replenish your energy. You can only sleep if you are tired enough. Using sleeping pills will allow you to forcefully sleep.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Eating many meals and taking sleep inducing drugs will make you feel tired and get rest at the end of the day. However, if you are eating small meals and use energy drinks or caffeine tablets often, you'll have a hard time being tired enough to sleep at the end of the day and will have a chance of waking up early.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_traders">
		<text>Trader Progression</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_traders_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Trader Progression\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A.'s trader progression system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Traders will mostly sell supplies and some accessories.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You won't be able to buy or sell armors and guns at traders.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can increase a trader's supply level by doing tasks for that trader's faction. The goodwill thresholds are 500, 1000, 1500 and 2000 goodwill. This is a reliable way to secure a steady income of quality ammunition.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Traders are either of the WP (Warsaw Pact) or NATO type. This will influence the kind of supplies they sell (mostly ammo and attachments).\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• NATO Factions: %c[ui_gray_2]Mercenaries, Clear Sky, Freedom and UNISG\n
		%c[pda_white]• Warsaw Pact Factions: %c[ui_gray_2]Military, Loners, Duty, Bandits, Renegades and Monolith.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]This designation also influences NPC loadouts, ie: Monolith NPCs have about a 50% chance to have a NATO or WP gun.\n
		Some traders sell very specific items, like Prof. Sakharov and Hermann selling the Artefacts Melter, a GAMMA specific toolkit that lets you empower and craft artefacts. They also sell exoskeleton PSU recipes at Supplies Lv 5.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_story">
		<text>Storylines &amp; Missions</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_story_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Storylines &amp; Missions\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Information on G.A.M.M.A.'s available questlines are as follows:\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Lost to the Zone:\n
		%c[pda_white]Available at your faction leader in your starting base with these factions:
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Loner\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Clear Sky\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Duty\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Freedom\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Mercenary\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ecologist\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Mission Afterglow:\n
		%c[pda_white]Available at the start of the UNISG playthrough (type "isg" during character creation to unlock faction).\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Artefact Hunters:\n
		%c[pda_white]To start this plot, talk to any NPC among the "Artefact Hunters", ie; Kovalev in the church in the Swamps or their representative named Sarik the Twilight in the Cordon Village.\n
		Available to Ecologist Allies:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Loner\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Clear Sky\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Duty\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Freedom\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Military\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Mercenary\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ecologist\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Last Dawn:\n
		%c[pda_white]Talk to Spire in the Swamps Clear Sky base. Available to Clear Sky Allies:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Loner\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Clear Sky\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Duty\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Freedom\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Mercenary\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ecologist\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Operation Monolith Retribution:\n
		%c[pda_white]Available from Colonel Kuzentsov. Available to Military Allies:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Military\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ecologist\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Dr.X Questline:\n
		%c[pda_white]Available to all factions. Not really story-oriented.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_repgun">
		<text>Repairs: Guns</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_repgun_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Repairs: Guns\n \n 
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A.'s weapon repair system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Guns must be repaired to progress since you cannot buy them from traders within GAMMA. You can loot guns from stashes or dead stalkers though. This is how you will make it to the North in one piece.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Most guns will be destroyed and will need to be fixed, or they will jam very often. Keep in mind that a gun's condition is separate from its parts condition.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Gun condition represents how clean a gun is and will change parts degradation and promote jamming. Jams are due to the quality of the actual gun parts. Repairing the gun's condition will not repair the gun's parts. Each part must be repaired individually with each part affecting the gun jamming frequency.\n
		The barrel changes the damage the gun deals and the strength of ammo penetration. A gun with a very bad barrel condition will deal almost no damage.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]You may repair guns in two ways:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can get the appropriate repair kit, %c[pda_white]right-click %c[ui_gray_2]the gun and choose "maintain parts". This will allow you to replace the parts for parts of greater condition but will consume a repair kit use. This can even replace barrels. These kits can be crafted or bought from mechanics once you have the appropriate toolkit (basic, advanced or expert). Replacing parts that way will improve the gun's condition.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can however still repair guns without the proper repair kits. Collect parts above 60% condition and repair them with the appropriate tool to 100% condition (Ramrod, Multitool, or File). Then simply drag and drop the repaired parts on to the gun. Moving parts in and out of the gun this way will make it less clean. Note that barrels cannot be replaced this way.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]If a gun has a barrel with a condition above 60%, you can buy a cleaning kit from mechanics, %c[pda_white]right-click %c[ui_gray_2]the gun and choose "%c[pda_white]clean barrel%c[ui_gray_2]". This goes the same for other parts. It's an easy way to get good guns early since you can buy cleaning kit without any toolkits needed. You must also clean the gun using cleaning equipment or pay a mechanic to do it. Cleaning a gun will not repair its parts but will prevent parts from degrading while shooting.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_reparm">
		<text>Repairs: Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_reparm_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Repairs: Armor\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A.'s armor repair system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Armor repair follow a similar pattern to guns. Find armor in stashes or on dead stalkers.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]To replace armor parts, you'll need armor above 50% condition and the appropriate repair kit in your inventory.  Below that, you'll need to change the parts.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Replace armor parts using a workbench or by %c[pda_white]right-clicking %c[ui_gray_2]any toolkit to open the workbench and open the repair menu. Replacing parts will not consume repair kits uses. From 50% and above, armor can be repaired directly using repair kits. Be sure to maintain your armor condition often with repair items.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Note that in GAMMA, mechanics cannot repair armor.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_rfpacks">
		<text>Packages</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_rfpacks_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Hidden Radio Emitting Packages\n \n
		%c[pda_white]The basics of G.A.M.M.A.'s RF package system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You'll get random messages that tell you to find some packages within certain maps. To find them, equip your RF Receiver and press the 'detector key'. Put your weapon away and change the frequency of your RF Receiver to match the one from the message (%c[pda_white]check keymap for more details%c[ui_gray_2]).\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Follow the strong beeps; the faster they are, the closer you are to the package.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can hold the Use button (%c[pda_white]F%c[ui_gray_2]) to display the package text and more easily find and grab it. It's actually an item laying on the ground or hidden in barrels, etc. It is NOT a stash you have to interact with.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]You can then %c[pda_white]right-click %c[ui_gray_2]the package in your inventory and open it to get its contents. Packages range from random stuff to artefacts or toolkits.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="article_gamma_ballistics">
		<text>Ballistics System</text>
	</string>
	<string id="article_gamma_ballistics_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Ballistics System\n \n
		%c[pda_white]GAMMA uses Grok's Balanced Overhaul Of Ballistic System. The basics of G.A.M.M.A.'s ballistics system are as follows:\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Notably, it changes the bullets and armor penetration from PLAYER to NPCs (not the other way around) using EFT's ammunition system as an inspiration. The goal is to have a more realistic ballistic system where you must consider the armor of your enemy, and the ammo type you are using.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ammo Armor Penetration (AP) power is compared to the limb armor of the opponent. If the AP power > limb armor, damage is applied. If AP power is less than limb armor, no damage is applied, and limb armor is reduced based on AP power.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Ammo with low AP power thus need to break an opponent’s limb armor before doing damage. AP ammo is thus required to kill heavily armored targets. FMJ and HP ammo will still work, but the enemy armor must be destroyed by many of these bullets before any damage can be done. Leg and face armor are reduced.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]AP Ammo (Armor Penetrating):\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Expensive but will defeat any endgame heavily armored target.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]These are considered end game ammo. Using them against lightly armored targets is ill-advised.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]FMJ Ammo (Full Metal Jacket):\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Cheap and should be used to kill lightly armored targets or as a cheaper and less effective replacement for AP ammo against armored targets.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]HP Ammo (Hollow-Point):\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]A bit more expensive than FMJ. Should be used to kill mutants since it has even less AP power than FMJ ammo.\n \n
		%c[pda_yellow]Other\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Sniper ammo is actually very powerful, but also very expensive. .338 Lapua will one shot most enemies with a hit to the chest.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Buckshot will work as inexpensive, early game ammo against stalkers. Forget about it mid and late game though. Good for mutants, bad for exos.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Slugs are good to kill mutants and stalkers alike. AP Slugs are best against stalkers.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Some ammo is much more useful against mutants, such as HP, .357 magnum, .45 Hydra-Shok, buckshot, slugs and 7.62x25 Pst.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Bullets have an armor penetration value in their description. This is based on the %c[pda_white]Russian BR %c[ui_gray_2]classification for ammo penetration:\n
		%c[pda_white]• BR1 %c[ui_gray_2]- %c[pda_white]BR2 %c[ui_gray_2]= %c[pda_white]penetrates light armor\n
		%c[pda_white]• BR3 %c[ui_gray_2]- %c[pda_white]BR4 %c[ui_gray_2]= %c[pda_white]penetrates middle-class armor\n
		%c[pda_white]• BR5 %c[ui_gray_2]= %c[pda_white]penetrates heavy armor\n
		%c[pda_white]• BR6 %c[ui_gray_2]= %c[pda_white]penetrates exo armor\n \n
		%c[pda_white]Some factions have specific characteristics:
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Monolith only uses AP ammo.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Sin only uses AP ammo, heavy machine guns and are much more resistant than a normal human.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]ISG members have very good gear, only use AP ammo and have a higher ammo penetration resistance.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Most Master and Legend stalkers use AP ammo.\n
		%c[pda_white]• %c[ui_gray_2]Factions use guns according to their trader type (WP or NATO).
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
