<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<string id="st_af_atom_name">
		<text>Atom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_atom_descr">
		<text>A beautiful artefact that consists of four small, multicolored spheres orbiting a larger translucent center. It gives off a slight amount of heat and can convert small doses of radiation in the body into usable energy.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ball_name">
		<text>Ball</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ball_descr">
		<text>A spherical artefact formed in electrical anomalies under unknown conditions. Very bouncy. If a person equips it and then kicks a mutant of the Zone, the artefact will smite the mutant, using its potential energy to send it flying.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_bat_name">
		<text>Bat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_bat_descr">
		<text>A bewildering, but unmistakable sight in the Zone. Consisting of two glowing, purple, bat-like "wings" apparently shielding an internal orb. When placed against another artefact, the Bat transmutes it into a more powerful similar artefact. The Bat is destroyed in the process, seemingly converted into pure energy.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_lighthouse_name">
		<text>Beacon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_lighthouse_descr">
		<text>The Beacon, or Lighthouse, is a yo-yo-shaped fibrous mass containing a very dense, continuously orbiting ball. If its user kills another being, they will be instantly teleported to the exact place where the victim's life ended.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_black_angel_name">
		<text>Black Angel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_black_angel_descr">
		<text>This artefact resembles a luminous clump of roots. When undisturbed, it will begin to release pure water vapor. When a person uses it, there is a small chance that any harm or pain inflicted upon them will instead be inflicted upon the attacker.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_chelust_name">
		<text>Chain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_chelust_descr">
		<text>A loop of tiny, glowing disks that generate a gravitational field disproportionately larger than their actual mass, leading to the artefact being effectively quite heavy. This artefact seems to be tied to a group of cultists in the Zone known as Sin, improving their health when they equip it.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_cocoon_name">
		<text>Cocoon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cocoon_descr">
		<text>A lattice-like structure with a film covering the gaps, formed in gravitational anomalies. When equipped, it causes the skin to temporarily harden in response to physical trauma, impeding mobility but reducing harm.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_cell_name">
		<text>Cell</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cell_descr">
		<text>A porous sphere with a star-like formation spinning in the center. Originates in gravitational anomalies. If the user of this artefact were to be hit with a fast-moving object, the Cell would instantly atomize some of its mass, protecting its bearer, but resulting in minor radiation exposure.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_kogot_name">
		<text>Claw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kogot_descr">
		<text>A beautiful glass-like formation from electrical anomalies. Contrary to its delicate appearance, it imbues its user with a primal bloodlust, strengthening them in hand-to-hand combat and allowing them to tear attackers limb-from-limb.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_dragon_eye_name">
		<text>Dragon's Eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dragon_eye_descr">
		<text>Found near fire anomalies, with the appearance of a reptile's eye. If its bearer kills another being, there is a small chance that it will cause its body to violently detonate.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_elektron_name">
		<text>Electron</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_elektron_descr">
		<text>A room-temperature superconductor generated in electrical anomalies. When worn, an Electron will reroute excess electrical energy into nearby batteries, capacitors, and the like. It also allows this energy to be used physically by its user.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fountain_name">
		<text>Fountain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fountain_descr">
		<text>An artefact of presumably gravitational nature with a bizarre shape. Under a microscope, the surface of the item appears to be fractal, having unimaginably complex  microstructures all the way to the atomic level. If equipped, it will replenish a small portion of any money lost.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_generator_name">
		<text>Generator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_generator_descr">
		<text>Generates weak electric currents and a small electromagnetic field. When its bearer is exerting energy, the Generator will capture some of that energy and disperse it to nearby batteries.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_grapes_name">
		<text>Grapes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grapes_descr">
		<text>An amber-like mass with a slight yellow-green hue. Its user will feel more satisfied and healthy after eating.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_ear_name">
		<text>Heart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ear_descr">
		<text>Artefact with a bizarre shape. Within its core, a small structure shaped like a human body is visible. It grants the user an indomitable will to live, allowing survival and recovery from otherwise fatal injuries or blood loss.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fonar_name">
		<text>Lamp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fonar_descr">
		<text>An artefact with the appearance of a melting pyramid of ice; formed in electrical anomalies. Equipping it causes the artefact to "show" its wearer the location of valuables, using both visible light and RF waves.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_medallion_name">
		<text>Medal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medallion_descr">
		<text>An artefact unique in that it appears almost man-made. It is a green ring with 4 lobes rotating around a central core. Sometimes, when the wearer of the Medal is injured, their injury will be completely transferred to another person nearby.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_peas_name">
		<text>Moon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_peas_descr">
		<text>The Moon, or Pea Pod artefact, is a crescent-shaped, dimly-glowing mass. Within the rubbery outer cover, three pearlescent orbs with unique crystalline structures are visible. Users of this artefact report their circadian rhythm rapidly and completely inverting.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_moh_name">
		<text>Moss</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_moh_descr">
		<text>Sometimes resembling an Itcher artefact, and sometimes breaking down into a more nebulous form, this electrical artefact gives off a small but noticeable charge, similar to touching one's tongue to both terminals of a battery. When equipped, the user will be imbued with certain strengths upon consuming raw meat.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_star_phantom_name">
		<text>Phantom Star</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_star_phantom_descr">
		<text>A purple, plasma-like substance encased in a transparent, pulsating shell. When activated, it sends the user into a ghost-like state for a short period - completely imperceptible, but unable to interact with the world.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_sandstone_name">
		<text>Sandstone</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sandstone_descr">
		<text>Formed in anomalies at extreme temperatures, this artefact somehow resembles sedimentary rock under a microscope. Small amounts of gold are present within the small globes that make up the artefact. Equipping it grants great power after killing other living things, but also results in a loss of physical constitution and pain tolerance.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_zhelch_name">
		<text>Scar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_zhelch_descr">
		<text>An ellipsoid artefact with interesting psi properties. At first, its user will feel calm and relaxed, but as time passes, they will lose their mind. This state of madness is completely reversible, and the user will return to normal after the artefact is removed.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_serofim_name">
		<text>Seraphim</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_serofim_descr">
		<text>An electrical artefact that generates a magnetic field. It is made up of several translucent, blue layers surrounding a bright center. If its bearer were to be suddenly killed, this artefact would take their place and allow the user to go on living.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_signet_name">
		<text>Signet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_signet_descr">
		<text>The Signet, or Amulet, appears to be a simple stone several precise holes bored through it. Some Stalkers believe it brings good luck. In reality, it provides its user with a greater sense of well-being and allows the body to heal wounds faster when near a fire.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_kislushka_name">
		<text>Sourpuss</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kislushka_descr">
		<text>A hollow spherical formation resembling a transparent parchment covered with a layer of film. Pleasant to the touch. This artefact will drastically speed up the process of blood clotting, though this will also lead to the user needing more food to replenish the energy that it takes.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_spaika_name">
		<text>Spike</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_spaika_descr">
		<text>A gravitational artefact that resembles a Meat Chunk and a Jellyfish fused together. If its bearer makes continues hits with a weapon, they will become increasingly more effective. If the user misses, however, it will shock their nervous system.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_sun_name">
		<text>Sun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sun_descr">
		<text>A rare specimen generating an inexhaustible source of light. It allows a form of solar photosynthesis in its wearer.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_tapeworm_name">
		<text>Tapeworm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_tapeworm_descr">
		<text>While its structure seems impossibly fragile, this artefact, made of pure quartz, is actually quite resilient. If its user is attacked, the artefact will temporarily paralyze the threat.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

<!---
	UNUSED
-->

	<string id="st_af_vaselisk_name">
		<text>Basilisk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vaselisk_descr">
    <text>If you found this. something has gone horribly wrong.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_arty_save">
		<text>Eye of the Noosphere</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_arty_save_descr">
		<text>One of the most mysterious artefacts in the Zone, the Eye of the Noosphere can transport its wielder back in time, even to escape death. A tight squeeze of the artefact activates its ability, creating a restoration point to go back to on activation or death. Frequent use can cause the artefact to change colour, but if discharged too frequently it may cease to function altogether. The Eye gradually restores its power over time, supposedly being fueled by the anomalous energy of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_gimlet_name">
		<text>Gimlet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gimlet_descr">
		<text>The bowl-shaped petals of the artefact release a powerful gaseous stimulant resulting in a positive change in human hormones. If you found this. something has gone horribly wrong.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_geliy_name">
		<text>Helium</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_geliy_descr">
		<text>A product of electrical anomalies. It gives off a gaseous substance. If you found this. something has gone horribly wrong.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_fire_loop_name">
		<text>Knot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_loop_descr">
		<text>Created within a thermal anomaly. Has a bizarre tetrahedral appearance. Only rumors of disappearances, betrayal, and death surround this hellish artefact.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_skull_miser_name">
		<text>Miser's Skull</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_skull_miser_descr">
		<text>The remains of a human head, disfigured and fossilized by the Zone. The teeth appear to be made of a pure crystal stone. If its bearer kills another person, their money may be duplicated.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_af_repei_name">
		<text>Thistle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_repei_descr">
		<text>A relatively common sight within gravitational anomalies, this artefact resembles the Thorn, an artefact not discovered in many years. While the Thorn caused bleeding to its user, the Thistle causes it to their enemies, impeding clotting and thinning blood.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Perk Artefact\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>