<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<string id="csky_patch">
		<text>Patch (Clear Sky)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from a Clear Sky uniform.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="freedom_patch">
		<text>Patch (Freedom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from Freedom uniform.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_patch">
		<text>Patch (Loner)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from a Loner uniform.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecolog_patch">
		<text>Patch (Ecologist)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from an Ecologist uniform.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_patch">
		<text>Patch (Bandit)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from a Bandit uniform.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="duty_patch">
		<text>Patch (Duty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="duty_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from a Duty uniform.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_patch">
		<text>Patch (Monolith)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from a Monolith uniform.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="army_patch">
		<text>Patch (Army)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from a Ukrainian army uniform.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_patch">
		<text>Patch (Mercenary)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_patch_description">
		<text>An insignia torn from a Mercenary uniform.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_clearsky_fp">
		<text>Patch (Clear Sky)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_clearsky_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a sunrise against a clear blue sky, flanked by doves. The design is meant to communicate the faction's desire to heal the Zone, as well as its distaste for conflict. Clear Sky has asserted an aim to gradually reduce the frequency and severity of blowouts and other anomalous cataclysms.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_freedom_fp">
		<text>Patch (Freedom)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_freedom_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a green wolf set against a black background alongside the Ukrainian flag. The design is meant to communicate Freedom's social nature and love of the land alongside their staunch determination and collective predatory viciousness in battle.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_stalker_fp">
		<text>Patch (Loner)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_stalker_fp_descr">
		<text>Commonly worn by unaligned stalkers, this patch is deemed a collectible by Mercenaries, who exchange badges like this for spoils from a mysterious patron.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ecolog_fp">
		<text>Patch (Ecologist)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecolog_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a pair of golden wings set against a white and cyan background. The Zone's black market highly values Ecologist patches, as sewing one convincingly into a suit can allow a stalker to go almost anywhere without fear of molestation by other groups.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_bandit_fp">
		<text>Patch (Bandit)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bandit_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a cracked black skull set against a white shield. The design is meant to communicate that they are not mere thugs, but rather the lords of feudal mobs, bringing order to those who accept their "protection" and bringing ruthless retribution upon anyone who dares defy them.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dolg_fp">
		<text>Patch (Duty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_dolg_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a gold crosshair set against a red and black shield. The design is meant to allude to the faction's military roots, without detracting from their chief role as the stoic soldiers who resolutely contend the Zone's every move for the sake of the world outside.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_monolith_fp">
		<text>Patch (Monolith)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_monolith_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts feathered wings set against a golden sun. The very existence of this patch suggests that Monolith troops either retain a higher level of creativity than initially thought, or an outside force is covertly outfitting them. Monolith patches are prized among other groups, as they demonstrate the ability to fight against the Monolith and live.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_army_fp">
		<text>Patch (Military)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_army_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a full military coat of arms with three heater shields. The centermost, the colours of the Ukrainian flag with two swords in saltire behind it. Encircling these shields are golden laurels. The Military forces in the Zone seem to fancy themselves as protectors and peacekeepers first and foremost.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_merc_fp">
		<text>Patch (Mercenary)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_merc_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts an azure bird of prey set against a black background. It is meant to be indicative of the Mercenary's character as a faction of cold, precise, highly mobile soldiers of fortune, ready to capture or terminate their objectives at a moment's notice.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_isg_fp">
		<text>Patch (UNISG)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_isg_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a white microscope girded by highly angular, stylized laurels set against a maroon background. Sewn onto the back of the patch is a label stating that the badge belongs to the United Nations International Scientific Group.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_greh_fp">
		<text>Patch (Sin)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_greh_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a serpent in the top-left corner with an Eastern Orthodox Cross in the top-right. Against the center of the badge sits a stylized image of an eclipse.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_renegade_fp">
		<text>Patch (Renegades)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_renegade_fp_descr">
		<text>This faction insignia depicts a jaundiced-looking scorpion set against a lush green shield. This item existing would imply the Zone's renegades once possessed a higher goal, although no one today would believe they would band together out of anything but sheer desperation. Still, this item is kept in circulation among all true Renegades, possibly out of nostalgia.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>