<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

<!-- Miscellaneous gear -->
	<string id="st_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psy-helmet (Calibrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>A psy-helmet with the ability to withstand the unusual mind-altering psy-frequencies of the various DUGA emitters within the Chernobyl Exclusion Zone, developed under the leadership of Sakharov at the research station near Yantar. When activated, the helmet projects an invisible dome near the user, acting on the energized particles released by the Shell artefact, thanks to which most of the radiation is extinguished, with remnants being reflected by the protection system built directly into the helmet’s body.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Quest Item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_bad_psy_helmet_name">
		<text>Psy-Helmet (Uncalibrated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bad_psy_helmet_desc">
		<text>An uncalibrated psy-helmet with the ability to withstand the unusual mind-altering psy-frequencies of the various DUGA emitters within the Chernobyl Exclusion Zone, developed under the leadership of Sakharov at the research station near Yantar. When activated, the helmet projects an invisible dome near the user, acting on the energized particles released by the Shell artefact, thanks to which most of the radiation is extinguished, with remnants being reflected by the protection system built directly into the helmet’s body.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Quest Item\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
<!-- Headgear -->
	<string id="st_helm_exo_name">
		<text>ExoHelmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_exo_descr">
		<text>The Exohelm is a thick steel helmet produced in the same Ukrainian factories as the exoskeleton armors. The accompanying gas mask is a British SF10, which can easily be found on the surplus markets after they were replaced for the General Service Respirator (GSR).\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_battle">
		<text>Sphere M12 Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_dolg">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12 Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_freedom">
		<text>Freedom Sphere M12 Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_battle_descr">
		<text>An aluminium/titanium helmet with a cloth exterior for camouflage. Comes with pockets that can be filled with additional armor pieces. This helmet is in common use among military stalkers and Spetsnaz, who typically use it in tandem with PSZ-series body armor. Overall, the M12 Sphere Helmet provides some of the best combat-oriented protection in the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_hardhat">
		<text>Surplus Steel Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_hardhat_descr">
		<text>An outdated steel army helmet with a retractable visor.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_protective">
		<text>SSP-99 Screen Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_protective_descr">
		<text>A high quality curtain helmet made by the same Defense Research Institute as the SSP-99 and SEVA bodysuits. Allows for complete isolation from the conditions of an anomalous environment. A closed-cycle air filtration system supplies the wearer with consistently cool, clean air.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_respirator">
		<text>Refitted PBF Gas Mask Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_freedom">
		<text>Freedom PBF Gas Mask Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_dolg">
		<text>Duty PBF Gas Mask Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_descr">
		<text>A ShMB gas mask refitted with external 40mm filters for greater functionality. As a general rule, masks like this offer respectable protection in areas of increased radioactivity, but suffer from a high failure rate in toxic environments.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_resp">
		<text>Respirator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_resp_descr">
		<text>A basic plastic and rubber respirator, used to protect the wearer from inhaling harmful dusts, fumes, vapors or gases. Widely used by rookies due to its light weight and economical environmental protection. However, it provides negligible physical protection and is guaranteed to fail in more heavily irradiated areas.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp5">
		<text>GP-5 Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_respirator_gp5_descr">
		<text>Originally built with the intention to protect the Soviet people from radioactive fallout. The filters of this GP-5 have been restored with a great deal of care. Compared to gas mask kits of similar price and availability, this reconditioned respiratory device boasts greater protection against radiation, but an even greater failure rate in toxic environments.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_bandana">
		<text>Bandana</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_bandana_descr">
		<text>An ordinary fabric bandana worn by conscripts, support corps and rear-echelon troops in the Military. Stalkers will often drape it around their mouth and nose to avoid breathing in toxic or radioactive particles but this protection is unreliable at best.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_rp_bala">
		<text>Balaclava</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_rp_bala_descr">
		<text>A regular black fabric balaclava. Stalkers will often drape it around their mouth and nose to avoid breathing in toxic or radioactive particles but this protection is unreliable at best.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_cloth_mask">
		<text>Cloth Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_cloth_mask_descr">
		<text>A simple piece of cloth, folded into a mask. Stalkers will often drape it around their mouth and nose to avoid breathing in toxic or radioactive particles but this protection is unreliable at best.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_m40">
		<text>M40 Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_m40_descr">
		<text>Provides respectable radiation and chemical protection for extended periods, even after suffering damage. Comes equipped with a multilayered 40-millimetre breathing filter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_metro">
		<text>"Apocalypse" Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_metro_descr">
		<text>Believed to have first been created by a faction known as "Final Day", this helm resembles a Czech M10 Gas Mask with heavy armor plating modifications. When the faction was dissolved, these helmets gradually entered into circulation.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_helm_tactic">
		<text>Sphere-08 Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_helm_tactic_descr">
		<text>A modern, high quality helmet with a built-in air filtration system based on Western models. The design consists of several layers of Kevlar and composite dielectric materials. Most commonly used by the Zone's Spetsnaz operators, especially in conjunction with the PS5 body armor series.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="helm_spartan">
		<text>Cz-M10 Spartan Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_spartan_descr">
		<text>A helmet commissioned by extremely influential stalkers, based off the design of the 'Apocalypse' helmet formerly used by the faction, "Final Day". In comparison, this helmet is lighter and more protective than its predecessor, comparing favorably to modern combat helmets such as the 'Sphere' series.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_redline">
		<text>Duty Sphere M12 "Red Line"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_battle_redline_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_vintage">
		<text>PSM-4 Combat Helmet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_vintage_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_ach7">
		<text>ACH-7 Headgear Set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ach7_descr">
		<text>The ACH-7 (Advanced Compound Headgear, 7 Parts) is a more modern version of the surplus steel helmet. Though, its lack of a respiratory device makes it an extremely poor choice for the Zone's conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_ach7ex">
		<text>ACH-7EX Headgear Set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ach7ex_descr">
		<text>The ACH-7 (Advanced Compound Headgear, 7 Parts) is a more modern version of the surplus steel helmet. The ACH-7EX comes with the inclusion of a respiratory system, boasting chemical and radiological protection somewhere between that of a GP-5 and a PBF kit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_eo21">
		<text>EO-21 PBFM Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_eo21_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21_red">
		<text>EO-21 PBFM Krasnyy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21_red_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_eo21sawnoff">
		<text>EO-21 PBFL Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_eo21sawnoff_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21sawnoff">
		<text>Duty EO-21 PBFL</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_eo21sawnoff_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_gp5">
		<text>GP-5 Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_gp5_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_ppm88">
		<text>PPM-88 Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ppm88_descr">
		<text>A Russian gas mask well suited for CBRN ecological hazards. In the Zone, it can be considered a functional and spiritual successor to the GP-5.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_m50">
		<text>M50z Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_m50_descr">
		<text>An M50 gas mask tweaked for better functionality in the Zone. Overall, it is considered an improvement over the M40.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_ranger">
		<text>GP-10z Ranger Gas Mask</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_ranger_descr">
		<text>Using the GP-10 as its model, this gas mask was designed primarily to protect the wearer from Controllers and Poltergeists.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="helm_dolg_tactic_red">
		<text>Duty Sphere 08 Krasnyy</text>
	</string>
	<string id="helm_dolg_tactic_red_descr">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Novice outfits -->
	<string id="novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A warm leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. The outfit of choice among naive or inexperienced stalkers. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="novice_outfit_camo_name">
		<text>Firearm Enthusiast's Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_camo_description">
		<text>A warm leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. Formerly owned by a typical firearm enthusiast, it sports several advantages over an ordinary jacket, namely a camouflage pattern, higher quality material and more pockets to hold belongings. Still an inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="novice_outfit_tourist_name">
		<text>Tourist’s Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="novice_outfit_tourist_description">
		<text>A warm leather anorak with an integrated backpack, worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. It seems the previous owner really loved hiking. The educated choice of materials and weight management system makes this more useful than most leather jackets. Still an inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Clear Sky Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A soft blue leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. These simple suits are assembled in large quantities by Clear Sky's tailors for use within the faction. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Duty Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A dark leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and combat boots. Formerly used only as relaxed wear for off-duty Dutyers, these simple suits were never intended for use by those on active service. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Black Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A black leather jacket commonly associated with the Zone's bandits and crooks. Mostly worn to intimidate rookies from other factions, it provides very little protection. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_novice_alt_outfit_name">
		<text>Armored Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_novice_alt_outfit_description">
		<text>Jackets like this first entered circulation among Bandits thanks to Quartermaster Morgan, a corrupt supplier who formerly belonged to the Duty faction. Offers protection comparable to a standard Military service outfit. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="redline_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Redline Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="redline_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A snazzy bright red leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and hiking boots. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>Freedom Leather Jacket</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A camouflaged leather anorak worn over a turtleneck sweater, tucked into jeans and combat boots. Such attire is typically only worn by Freedomers. An inadequate choice for the Zone's harsh conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Overcoats -->
	<string id="monolith_trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_freedom_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Freedom Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_dolg_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Duty Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_outfit_description">
		<text>A long, thick overcoat.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="trenchcoat_brown_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Brown Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_brown_outfit_description">
		<text>A long, thick overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. Although the closed-cycle system and several other features seem to have been stripped off, the end result still compares favorably to many basic stalker suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="trenchcoat_green_outfit_name">
		<text>Heavy Green Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="trenchcoat_green_outfit_description">
		<text>A long, thick green overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. Although the closed-cycle system and several other features seem to have been stripped off, the end result still compares favorably to many basic stalker suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_trenchcoat_outfit_name">
		<text>Sin Heavy Overcoat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_trenchcoat_outfit_description">
		<text>A long, thick, bloodstained overcoat worn over a butchered scientist suit. Although the closed-cycle system and several other features seem to have been stripped off, the end result still compares favorably to many basic stalker suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	

<!-- Exploration -->
	<string id="travel_outfit_name">
		<text>"Voyager" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="travel_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. This particular outfit is of high quality and is intended for extended exploration within the Zone. A suit of choice for many artefact and mutant hunters.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="nomad_outfit_name">
		<text>"Nomad" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nomad_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. This particular outfit is of high quality and feels exceptionally light and comfortable to wear. It is clear that whoever assembled this armor was highly familiar with the Zone's nature, and evidently put a great deal of pride and care into their work.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="antirad_outfit_name">
		<text>GP-5MvC Anti-rad Bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="antirad_outfit_description">
		<text>Developed and designed by frequent visitors of the 100 Rads and the Barkeep, who supported the project financially, the design was based off of the Sunrise suit. A common and old but still reliable GP-5 gas mask is integrated with lightweight oxygen tanks carried on the back.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="hybrid_outfit_name">
		<text>Hybrid Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="hybrid_outfit_description">
		<text>A suit created by one of Kiev's defence research institutes for the purpose of guarding researchers in the Zone. However, it is clear the suit was created on a budget. As such, none of these suits were ever officially commissioned by the Ukrainian government, although a few managed to find their way into the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="wastelander_outfit_name">
		<text>"Wastelander" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="wastelander_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. This particular outfit is unusually light compared to average stalker suits, but possesses a spacious Class IIIA vest and lightweight inserts. It's essentially a more nimble, stalker-made Berill-5M suit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

<!-- CS outfits -->
	<string id="csky_light_novice_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-1 Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_light_novice_outfit_description">
		<text>A light suit worn by Clear Sky's novice researchers. It provides more than adequate protection from the anomalous phenomena found within the Swamps.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="csky_light_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2a Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_light_outfit_description">
		<text>An upgrade to the CS-1 bodysuit intended for conducting rapid search operations in areas of low risk.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_medium_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-3a Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_medium_outfit_description">
		<text>A heavier but still comfortable outfit worn by members of Clear Sky that provides more than adequate protection, especially in combat.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="csky_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-3b Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="csky_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>Formerly the standard outfit issued to Clear Sky assault squads, after the faction’s infamous failure against the NPP in 2011, this armor serves as a reminder that even an excellent protective bodysuit cannot guarantee safety on the wrong side of the perimeter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	

<!-- NBC outfits -->
	<string id="nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Tactical Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>A 'Sunrise' stalker suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. A solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="monolith_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Tactical Monolith Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>A Monolith suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. A solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2t Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>A CS-2b stalker suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. A solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Load-bearing 'Twilight' Tactical Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>A Mercenary 'Twilight' suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. A solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>Keeper of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_freedom_outfit_description">
		<text>A Sentinel of Freedom suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. A solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="nbc_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-Mt Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="nbc_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>A PS5-M suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. A solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_nbc_outfit_name">
		<text>Load-bearing 'Sunset' Tactical Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_nbc_outfit_description">
		<text>A 'Sunset' bandit suit with the vest switched out for a special pocketed load-bearing alternative. A solid suit for a scavenger on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
<!-- Assault vest -->
	<string id="light_loner_outfit_name">
		<text>Interceptor Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_loner_outfit_description">
		<text>An old IBA suit imported from the West and modified for the Zone's conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="light_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>Defender of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_freedom_outfit_description">
		<text>Rumored to be supplied to the Freedom faction directly from an unknown source, this suit is based on the somewhat outdated IBA system, but modified for greater comfort when operating in the Zone's conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_voen_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Stalker IBAz Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_voen_outfit_description">
		<text>An Interceptor Anomalous Body Armor System that ended up in the hands of the Military. Compared to the standard model, this suit is slightly more ergonomic and boasts greater protection against psychic interference.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_monolit_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith IBAz Assault Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_monolit_outfit_description">
		<text>An Interceptor Anomalous Body Armor System that ended up in the hands of the Monolith. Compared to the standard model, this suit is slightly more ergonomic and boasts greater protection against psychic interference.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>IBAz Universal Protection Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>An old IBA suit imported from the West and modified for the Zone's conditions. Uncomfortably heavy, the Duty variant seems to have received extensive upgrades for protection against chemical weapons.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="light_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary IBAz Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>A well-kept Interceptor Anomalous Body Armor System sold directly to the Mercenaries from various Western sources. While a little uncomfortable, this suit is overall better than the standard model circulating around the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="light_isg_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG IBAz Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="light_isg_outfit_description">
		<text>A strong but somewhat outdated combat suit. Considered the bare minimum of what should be worn in situations where conflict with armed SSU forces seems inevitable.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Sunrise suits -->
	<string id="stalker_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunrise" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. The Sunrise is one of the oldest stalker suits in existence. It is also widely considered the bare minimum protection a stalker should have for serious trips into the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_outfit_camo_name">
		<text>"Chameleon" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_camo_description">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="stalker_outfit_alt_name">
		<text>"Hipster" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_outfit_alt_description">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_drought_outfit_name">
		<text>"Drought" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_drought_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. For a stalker suit, the "Drought" possesses above-average ballistic protection, but is considerably less comfortable to wear.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_predator_outfit_name">
		<text>"Predator" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_predator_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. An overall upgrade over the "Drought" suit and significantly more comfortable to wear. The "Predator" enjoys popularity among greenhorns and experts alike thanks to its low maintenance costs and great modification potential.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_autumn_outfit_name">
		<text>"Autumn" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_autumn_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. Favoured among newer artefact hunters and creative hit men, the "Autumn" allows easier traversal of chemical anomalous fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_vineleaf_outfit_name">
		<text>"Vineleaf" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_vineleaf_outfit_description">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_bear_outfit_name">
		<text>"Bear" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_bear_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. The suit's improved protection against ballistics has been achieved through an unnamed home-made anomalous compound.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_salamander_outfit_name">
		<text>"Salamander" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_salamander_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. An economical choice with great upgrade potential. Ironically, for being dubbed the "Salamander", it demonstrates a poor ability to safely channel heat.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_graphite_outfit_name">
		<text>"Graphite" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_graphite_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. It was independently designed by a few optimistic stalkers who were expecting to take measurements of psy-storms out in the open. Naturally, this endeavour failed, but their designs were later recovered and used to produce a stalker suit able to shelter the wearer's nervous system.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="stalker_tigerstripe_outfit_name">
		<text>"Tigerstripe" Stalker Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_tigerstripe_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by local craftsmen. One of the heavier stalker suits available, this outfit was designed for those who prefer to make their money as hired killers or fighters instead of looting artefacts or skinning mutants.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecologist_guard_outfit_name">
		<text>ISRIT Guard Jumpsuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecologist_guard_outfit_description">
		<text>A basic suit originally intended as spare equipment for Professor Hermann's "Iskra Scientific Research and Investigation Team", it has since become a relatively cheap protective bodysuit for Ecologist guards working all over the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_stalker_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2b Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_stalker_outfit_description">
		<text>Unlike other suits in the CS-1, 2 and 3 series, this body armor was only created after the faction's massive losses at the Chernobyl NPP. It is widely considered to be the first proper successor to the CS-1 suit as it focuses on keeping the wearer safe from anomalous environments over armoring them for battle.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- STS (Special Tactical Suits) -->
	<string id="svoboda_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Wind of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_light_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, handmade by Freedom craftsmen. This comfortable bodysuit has been treated with a special solution known as 'Horizon', to increase resistance to chemical anomalies.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith X-18 Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_outfit_description">
		<text>A mysterious bodysuit associated with the Monolith faction. Previously of unknown origin, scores of these suits were found in containers and lockers underneath the X18 facility in Dark Valley. There are theories among stalkers that these suits predate the creation of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_sun_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunset" Tactical Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_sun_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, made by local craftsmen. Its design bears resemblance to a Monolith X-18 suit with its conventional NBC features stripped down in favor of greater insulation from thermal and electrical threats. Mostly used by Bandits in Dark Valley to clear out the poltergeists that occasionally escape from the local lab.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_sun_outfit_name">
		<text>"Twilight" Tactical Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_sun_outfit_description">
		<text>A Zone-assembled suit, made by local craftsmen. Its design bears resemblance to a Monolith X-18 suit, an outfit the Mercs no doubt tried to salvage from their costly skirmishes in Limansk.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_nighthunter_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary STS-N Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_nighthunter_outfit_description">
		<text>Sometimes nicknamed the "Nighthunter", this outfit is a slightly heavy special tactical suit, used by Mercenaries in both nocturnal and urban combat scenarios.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_wolven_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary STS-W Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_wolven_outfit_description">
		<text>Sometimes nicknamed the "Wolven", this outfit is a comfortable special tactical suit, used by Mercenaries in both exploratory expeditions and stealth operations.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Mk1 Tactical Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_outfit_description">
		<text>Based on a fairly standard suit design used by Western special forces, outfits like this are common to many militaries throughout the world. This is the bare minimum a UNISG operative can expect to be fitted with.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Mk2 Tactical Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>An improvement over the original Mk-1 design, this outfit is much better suited for the Zone's conditions. These improvements were commissioned by UNISG based on the limited data that could be recovered from their less fortunate predecessors.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
<!-- LCS (Light Combat Suit) -->
	<string id="merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_outfit_description">
		<text>The "Light Combat" suit is one of the most common outfits used by the Zone's Mercenaries. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. Adequate for basic operations, but quality is lacking when compared to standard Spetsnaz gear.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_fighter_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC-F Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_fighter_outfit_description">
		<text>Referred to as the "Fighter" by Mercenaries, this suit is a variation of the standard LC outfit. It can perform surprisingly well in operations where stealth and speed are imperative.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="banditmerc_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced LC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="banditmerc_outfit_description">
		<text>A light combat suit obtained to help armor local Bandit gangs. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. In a twist of dramatic irony, it appears whoever supplied these suits were ripping off their customers as the build quality is significantly worse.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="renegademerc_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade LC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegademerc_outfit_description">
		<text>A light combat suit obtained through shady means to help armor local groups of Renegades. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. Surprisingly pleasant to wear.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_sunset_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LCz Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_sunset_outfit_description">
		<text>A Mercenary Light Combat Suit modified for use in the Zone. This suit is a genuine improvement for most newer Mercenaries and not a bad alternative to the faction's special tactical suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scout_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LC-S Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scout_outfit_description">
		<text>Nicknamed the "Scout", this outfit is an LC-F suit modified to fill a more specialized niche. A very comfortable suit. Its modifications make it a good choice for Mercenaries who want to explore the Zone's anomalies on a budget.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_jackal_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary LTS-J Body Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_jackal_outfit_description">
		<text>A light tactical suit, nicknamed "Jackal" after the now dead Merc leader who was assigned to crack open the X-8 laboratory over six years ago. Being marvelously comfortable with a fairly sophisticated weight distribution system, it is a favorite among more experienced Mercenaries.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_coyote_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary MTS-C Body Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_coyote_outfit_description">
		<text>A medium tactical suit, nicknamed the "Coyote". Widely considered the successor of the LTS-J body suit. Naturally, its price is higher than that of its predecessor, but this won't stop most Mercs from springing for it when they are able.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="greh_armored_outfit_name">
		<text>Irij Flak Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_armored_outfit_description">
		<text>A comfortable and ergonomic arming suit used to outfit Sin's followers en masse. It consists of a ballistic vest over an environmental bodysuit. These suits do a good job fortifying the already durable warriors of Sin.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_armored_camo_outfit_name">
		<text>Vyriy Flak Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_armored_camo_outfit_description">
		<text>A more advanced variant of regular Sin flak armor, typically gifted to the faction's more loyal and devout members. These suits do a great job fortifying the already durable warriors of Sin.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_voin_outfit_name">
		<text>PS6-V Warrior Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_voin_outfit_description">
		<text>A modern, updated variant of the original PS5-M universal protection bodysuit. Is more than adequate for all of the Zone's conditions as well as being markedly comfortable for a Duty suit. Originally intended to replace its predecessor entirely, its higher production cost put this goal on hold in the face of Duty's multitude of recent losses.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_lcs_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_outfit_description">
		<text>A "Light Combat Suit" model adapted for use by UNISG troops. Its design is based on the one used by the special forces of Western armies.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_lcs_camo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC-C Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_camo_outfit_description">
		<text>A modified "Light Combat Suit" model adapted for use in the Zone by UNISG troops. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. Light weight and comfortable.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_lcs_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG LC-UC Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_lcs_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>A modified "Light Combat Suit" model adapted for use in battle by UNISG troops. Its design is based on the suit used by the special forces of Western armies. Compares favorably in combat compared to many other outfits in its class, but still falls short of what a Spetsnaz operator would be wearing.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Berill-5M Armored Suits -->
	<string id="army_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Service Outfit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_outfit_description">
		<text>A poor protective outfit contracted by government bureaucrats outsourcing to the lowest bidder. Typically issued to helicopter pilots, tank drivers, rear-echelon personnel, conscripts and enlisted servicemen.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="specops_outfit_name">
		<text>Berill-5M Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_outfit_description">
		<text>This outfit comprises military PS5 series body armor with beryllium sputter modified for use in the Zone. Designed for intense rapid-insertion assault operations, this outfit is standard issue for most Spetsnaz operators in the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="specops_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-B Battle Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>This outfit comprises military PS5 series body armor with beryllium sputter modified for use in the Zone. Compared to a standard PS5-M universal protection suit, this outfit is more ergonomic and protective overall.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="specops_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary B-5M Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>Spetsnaz body armor acquired and repurposed by the Zone's Mercenaries. Provides good physical protection while also being remarkably comfortable to wear. Often worn by Mercenaries who used to work for the SSU.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="specops_bandit_outfit_name">
		<text>Deserter's B-5M Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="specops_bandit_outfit_description">
		<text>A set of PS5 series body armor with beryllium sputter, acquired through shady means by the Zone's Bandits. Although the suit shows visible signs of irreparable wear and tear, it's still an excellent choice for battle.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>Guardian of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>A set of Spetsnaz body armor that has been "liberated" for use in the Freedom faction. This suit has been treated with "Sovereign", an anomalous compound invented by the faction. Any Freedomer expected to help defend the Barrier will do their best to get their hands on this suit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_specops_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-B2 Veteran Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_specops_red_outfit_description">
		<text>A set of former Spetsnaz body armor, bolstered with more substantial protection. An excellent combat bodysuit, although it has an infamous failure rate in areas of extreme anomalous activity. Despite this, Duty's veterans claim you do not need protection from anomalies once you know how to spot them.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- PS5-M Universal protection suit -->
	<string id="dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M Universal Protection Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>An old version of the Duty bodysuit, better suited for recruits who may prefer the familiarity of stalker suits over frontline battle armor.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scout_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-R Scout Vest</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scout_outfit_description">
		<text>An old Duty suit developed alongside the PS5-M universal protection outfit intended to protect Duty scouts in the early days of the Zone's existence. However, the only parts of the Zone left to be explored are far too dangerous for a light bodysuit like this. As such, these are mostly retired, kept in reserve only to outfit Duty recruits in desperate circumstances.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M Hunter Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_red_outfit_description">
		<text>A somewhat heavier variant of the PS5-M universal protection suit, specifically designed for Dutyers intending to hunt mutants. A small amount of ballistic protection is sacrificed in favor of much better protection against common mutant attacks. Compares well even to modern Duty suits.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_2_name">
		<text>Sentinel of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_heavy_outfit_2_description">
		<text>An aged, slightly heavier stalker bodysuit made long ago by Freedom craftsmen. Although the suit has obviously acquired some wear and tear in places, it's roughly on par with most other basic stalker suits, even today. Younger Freedomers will pay through the nose to acquire one of these outfits, simply because of the amazing stories these venerable suits have acquired over the years.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_ps5_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced PS5-M Universal Protection Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_ps5_outfit_description">
		<text>Armor like this first entered circulation among Bandits thanks to Quartermaster Morgan, a corrupt supplier who formerly belonged to the Duty faction. It gives up some of its physical protection for greater comfort and defence against anomalies. These suits are a major sore point for the Duty faction, and getting them out of the hands of anarchists, criminals and murderers is an unspoken priority.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_ps5_outfit_name">
		<text>Volos Flak Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_ps5_outfit_description">
		<text>This outfit's design is based on the PS5-M universal protection suit, though it is unknown how it has come into the possession of Sin. Nevertheless, Duty is not happy to know their armor designs are being appropriated by Zone worshiping fanatics and the recovery of these suits are an unspoken priority. The suit itself is of good quality, and is more than adequate for the Zone's conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	
<!-- Skat-9 Military Armored Suits -->
	<string id="military_outfit_name">
		<text>Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_monolit_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_freedom_outfit_name">
		<text>Liberated Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_sky_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-4b Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_bandit_outfit_name">
		<text>Looted Skat-9 Armored Suit</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="military_outfit_description">
		<text>An excellent protective suit for the Zone. This heavy military-grade armor is designed for major battle operations in anomalous areas. Comprises a PSZ-12p heavy military armored suit, built-in compensation suit, and an anomalous protection bodysuit. Although originally intended for the sole use of Military stalkers and experienced Spetsnaz operators, this armor occasionally finds its way into factions outside of the Military through unknown means.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_heavy_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9d Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_outfit_description">
		<text>Developed by defence research institutes in Kiev, the first iteration of this Duty bodysuit began as a simple old set of Spetsnaz PSZ-9 body armor, modified for the Zone. These days, this armor's latest design is capable of stopping a rifle bullet, and boasts great protection against the Zone's myriad horrors. It is uncommon for armor as prized as this to be issued to any Dutyer who hasn't proven themselves in some significant manner.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_pantsir_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-7p Shell Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_pantsir_outfit_description">
		<text>An "in-between" suit that is more protective than Duty's regular PS5 universal protection suit, yet cheaper and easier to produce than a proper set of PSZ-9d body armor. Ideal for skirmishes, its relative ease of maintenance and repair is a great boon to Dutyers far away from friendly territory, such as the investigators who venture up into Yanov or beyond.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_heavy_redline_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9kl Command Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_redline_outfit_description">
		<text>This suit was a favorite of the late Lieutenant Colonel Shulga, who rarely ventured outside his operational base in Yanov, yet constantly feared assassination at the hands of Freedom. Thus, heavy protection like this fitted his needs perfectly. As fate would have it, he'd instead later be presumed dead after leading a mass assault into Pripyat with his contingent of troops. Veteran Dutyers will occasionally wear suits like this to battle in his honour.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Scientific outfits -->
	<string id="scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>SEVA Bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>Designed and produced by one of Kiev's defence research institutes and represents an excellent alternative to hand-made stalker suits. It combines a CBRN jumpsuit with a specially-treated class II Kevlar vest. Due to the quality of materials used, this bodysuit sports good durability within ambient anomalous fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Watchman of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A suit of "Sentinel" body armor specially produced by Freedom craftsmen for observing anomalous phenomena in the Zone. The specially treated materials provide good protection and suit durability during prolonged exploration of anomalous fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>The Monolith scientific suit includes a flak vest of unknown origin and features unique modifications for greater resistances to radiation at the cost of being more vulnerable to psy-fields. Curiously, according to some legends, these suits are most often worn by the soldiers who defend the Brain Scorcher in Radar, although no one outside the Monolith faction can easily confirm.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-4a SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>An unofficial version of the SEVA scientific suit, fresh off the smuggling route. Typically used by groups of the Clear Sky faction.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_good_name">
		<text>CS-4a Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_scientific_outfit_good_description">
		<text>An unofficial version of the SEVA scientific suit that has been extensively improved by Novikov, Clear Sky's resident technician. Extremely comfortable to move around in, making it a high-demand suit among some factions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Looted SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>Bandits have never been terribly interested in the science and research of anomalous fields, but nevertheless, need protective suits such as these to organize ambushes and attacks on stalkers within anomalous fields and radiation pockets.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>Originally commissioned by the first iteration of UNISG from one of Kiev's defence research institutes for research in the Zone. The special treatment materials provide enhanced protection and durability against radiation and anomalous effects.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>A variant of the SEVA bodysuit that was commissioned by Mercenaries. Used by veteran Mercs on artefact-hunting contracts. Good protection for a SEVA suit but missing some of the newer psy-protection upgrades available in the newer SEVA models.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_combat_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_combat_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>As a token of goodwill and to help cover their research costs, Clear Sky occasionally makes coveted "Pathfinder" suits on commission for use among the Zone's Mercenaries. Compared to the stock SEVA suit, this model is superior across the board. Comes with a built-in Class IIIA ballistic vest.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md Universal Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>The Duty faction version of the standard SEVA suit. Like the standard suit variant, it consists of a durable anomaly-resistant CBRN jumpsuit and a specially-treated Class II Kevlar vest. A solid suit for extended dives into anomaly fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scientific_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md Light Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_red_outfit_description">
		<text>A lighter variant of the Duty scientific suit that has shed almost half its weight at the cost of slightly decreased protection. The ballistic armor has been replaced by a class IIA vest with numerous pockets.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_scientific_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-9Md Light Pathfinder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_scientific_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>As a token of goodwill and to help cover their research costs, Clear Sky occasionally makes coveted "Pathfinder" suits on commission for use among the Duty faction. Altered according to Duty's needs, its weight has been reduced by almost half at the expense of protection. Despite this, it's an excellent and comfortable outfit for Duty's more curious members.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_scientific_dark_outfit_name">
		<text>Patchwork Anomaly Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_scientific_dark_outfit_description">
		<text>A SEVA-like suit made from scratch by one of the Bandits' gifted craftsmen. Compared to the looted SEVAs that are brought in and restored, this patchwork outfit boasts average protection against anomalies while retaining a surprisingly low weight. Additionally, it's rather stylish and comfy, allowing it to become a hit among the criminals who can afford it.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="renegade_scientific_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade SEVA Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegade_scientific_outfit_description">
		<text>This comfortable bodysuit, originally intended for research in the Zone, makes for a great alternative to the various other light combat or hand-made suits readily available within the Zone. Compared to a standard SEVA suit, it provides improved protection against thermal hazards and blunt trauma. However, its other protective qualities are inferior to the original SEVA.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="merc_scientific_armored_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary SEVA Body Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_scientific_armored_outfit_description">
		<text>A variant of the SEVA bodysuit that was commissioned by Mercenaries. Used by veteran mercenaries who are expected to guide researchers and artefact hunters in the more dangerous parts of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_scientific_light_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Patchwork Science Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_scientific_light_outfit_description">
		<text>A SEVA-like suit made from scratch by an unknown craftsman. It is unknown what role this suit fills within the Monolith faction as a whole, although it's been speculated that it's purpose is largely ceremonial.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ace_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary ACE Scientific Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ace_outfit_description">
		<text>One of the most technologically advanced bodysuits in the Zone. The ACE armor system incorporates a next-generation CBRN and a pocketed Kevlar vest with Class III plate inserts. Using state of the art materials such as selectively-permeable coatings, this suit manages both maximal anomaly protection and wearer comfort. Used by only the most wealthy Mercenaries.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- SSP-99 -->
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_orange_name">
		<text>SSP-99 Bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_orange_description">
		<text>The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone's conditions and is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the SSP-99 screen helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. Its design is specifically tailored for maximum durability in thermal, chemical, and electrical fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_name">
		<text>SSP-99M Bodysuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_grn_description">
		<text>High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A Kevlar underlayer has been added to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. Provides improved protection from biological anomalies compared to the SSP-99.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_white_name">
		<text>SSP-99 "Diamond"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_white_description">
		<text>The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone's conditions and is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the SSP-99 screen helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. Its design is specifically tailored for maximum durability in thermal and chemical fields. The "Diamond" variant also gives superior protection from electricity.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_blue_name">
		<text>SSP-99M "Sapphire"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_blue_description">
		<text>High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A Kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. The "Sapphire" model provides excellent protection against short-range psi-emissions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_red_name">
		<text>SSP-99Ì "Ruby"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_red_description">
		<text>High quality modified SSP-99 suit. A Kevlar underlayer has been added to the suit to reduce the risk of suit puncture from hostile mutants. The "Ruby" model provides improved protection against melee attacks, and includes an integrated wound healing system.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_yello_name">
		<text>SSP-99 Topaz</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ecologist_outfit_yello_description">
		<text>The SSP-99 is a current-generation CBRN suit specially designed for the Zone's conditions and is used by scientific expeditions for extended forays into anomalous fields. When combined with the SSP-99 screen helmet, it includes an integrated air-filtering and air-conditioning system. The "Topaz" variant provides increased protection from radiation.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Heavy combat suits -->
	<string id="exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Duty Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This suit is typically found in the hands of elite Duty warriors, especially those assigned to guard VIPs or launch exceedingly dangerous raids on enemy stalkers.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Warrior of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Only the most respected members of Freedom will ever be found wearing a suit like this.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. An outfit of choice for the captains and bodyguards of Mercenary companies requiring top of the line ballistic protection.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Looted Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Both imposing and highly intimidating in appearance, this outfit is a favorite among the Zone's most powerful outlaws.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. A favorite among the Monolith's battle preachers and tactical masters who claim the confines of the suit to be as comforting as the Sarcophagus itself.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Stalker Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Considered too cumbersome by the Ukrainian government, these suits are never issued to any unit or individual. Thus soldiers, Military stalkers and the occasional veteran must always find and pay for it through their own means.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-5 Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. These outfits are smuggled in from Ukrainian factories near the borders of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_exolight_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_exolight_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. A rare sight, since most ISG operatives prefer increased mobility over raw protective power.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>Woodland Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This model includes an early-generation CBRN jumpsuit lined with Kevlar.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="bandit_exo_earth_outfit_name">
		<text>Fenced Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exo_earth_outfit_description">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="freedom_exo_vineleaf_outfit_name">
		<text>Hero of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_exo_vineleaf_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an old CBRN jumpsuit lined with Kevlar and an additional attachment slot.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Duty Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This suit is typically found in the hands of elite Duty warriors, especially those assigned to guard VIPs or launch exceedingly dangerous raids.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_red_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Venator Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_red_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This particular variant is typically found in the hands of elite Duty huntsmen, where its greater defense against mutants is utilized.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10l Forest Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an older CBRN jumpsuit with Kevlar weave and additional steel reinforcement. Typically found with elite Duty members, particularly those conducting short operations in the northern reaches of the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_dolg_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10g Urban Battlesuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_dolg_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. Old and exceedingly heavy, it's possible that suits like this were used by the Duty faction to raid Pripyat and clash with Freedom back in 2012.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Heavy Armor TB-1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_outfit_description">
		<text>.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_urban_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Urban Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_urban_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. Additionally, it is only useful in melee and ranged fights, since it offers no anomaly protection whatsoever. An outfit of choice for the captains and bodyguards of Mercenary companies operating in areas like Limansk or Pripyat.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_wood_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Woodland Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_wood_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an old CBRN that has unfortunately not been modified for the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="exo_merc_grass_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Grassland Exosuit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_merc_grass_outfit_description">
		<text>Also known as the "Radsuit", this outfit is essentially a heavy ballistic vest containing Class IV plates reinforced with steel with many of the attachment points needed for a rigid exoskeleton. However, with no powered exoskeleton to ease the load, this armor proves cumbersome to wear for extended periods of time. This variant includes an asbestos-weave jumpsuit.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Proptotype Exoskeleton -->
	<string id="stalker_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>"Sunrise" Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="stalker_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A stalker bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_light_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Wind of Freedom Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_light_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A Wind of Freedom bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PS5-M Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A PS5-M universal protection bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="dolg_heavy_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-9d Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_heavy_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A PSZ-9d armored bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it sacrifices raw ballistic protection for greater functionality in anomalous fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Skat-9 Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>The very first iteration of the military exoskeleton, modified to fit with the servos and batteries of a modern exoskeleton. Compared to a third-generation exo, it sacrifices raw ballistic protection for greater functionality in anomalous fields.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>X-18 Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An armor made by either Monolithians or an unknown manufacturer. It has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_stalker_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-2b Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_stalker_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A set of CS-2b body armor that has been specially modified to fit with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="ecolog_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>SSP-99M Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A unique armor system composed of an exoskeleton-powered SSP-99M jumpsuit with an anomaly-resistant Class IIA Kevlar vest placed on top. The durable exo-frames are capable of providing mechanical support for carrying heavy loads even through anomaly fields. Ideal for aiding researchers during deep incursions into the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="isg_proto_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Tactical Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_proto_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A UN-branded special tactical bodysuit, specially designed to be fitted with the servos and batteries of an exoskeleton, allowing the wearer to carry significantly more equipment than they could under any other circumstances. Compared to a full exoskeleton, it provides less protection, but is also considerably lighter.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	
<!-- Exoskeletons -->
	<string id="exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An experimental sample of a military exoskeleton consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Was never mass-produced due to extraordinary cost and some design flaws though small batches are made in underground facilities outside Ukraine.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="dolg_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="dolg_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>Excellent high-tech armor consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Domestically developed by one of the research institutes, specifically for the Duty faction. Is slowly being phased out in favor of cheaper, more practical suits, and the few Exosuits in active service tend to be in the hands of Duty's oldest veterans.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="svoboda_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Paragon of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="svoboda_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An excellent bodysuit produced by Freedom’s finest artisans consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. While not always the most practical suit to maintain, it is undeniably powerful, and as such is entrusted only to Freedom's finest warriors and guardsmen.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An experimental sample of a military exoskeleton of western production consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors.. While not always the most practical suit to maintain in the Zone, it simultaneously allows the wearer to be both heavily armed and extremely well armored, with enough strength to carry a weeks worth of supplies. Most often worn by veteran Mercenary captains expected to lead their men through hellish conditions.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>High-tech armor consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Study samples have revealed that its servos are made of alloys and materials unknown to any field of science in any other part of the world. Wearing this suit feels like being buried under the concrete of the Sarcophagus itself; terrifyingly claustrophobic for most stalkers, but eerily comforting for true servants of the Monolith.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="bandit_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Stolen Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="bandit_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>A stolen military exoskeleton customized by outlaws to attack well-guarded facilities and to plunder well-armed stalkers. More martially inclined aspiring Bandit Lords tend to favor this armor, using it as a stark and unquestionable symbol of their strength and authority over lesser criminals.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="military_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Stalker Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="military_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>The official military exoskeleton. Released in limited quantities by special order to Military stalkers who payed for it themselves. Designed to carry heavy weapons, along with enough ammunition, food and meds to keep the unit supplied for long periods of time. Occasionally fielded in lieu of light vehicles.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="cs_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>CS-5 Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="cs_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An experimental version of the army exoskeleton smuggled into the Zone from Ukrainian factories before being refurbished by Clear Sky technicians. Generally, suits like these are held in reserve, to be deployed only in times of true crisis. That said, especially trusted comrades and associates of the faction may eventually receive permission to acquire such a suit for their own personal uses, although not without great cost.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="ecolog_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Scientific Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ecolog_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>An official version of the military exoskeleton, intended for use by the Ecologists' guards. The suit feels almost impervious to small arms, and its advanced servomotors make it an excellent choice for those in entrenched defensive positions, as it greatly aids in the use of heavy defensive weaponry. When out in the field, wearers of this suit are more commonly used to carrying ludicrous amounts of batteries, LLMCs, AAMs and other supplies an accompanying scientist might need when exploring the Zone.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="renegade_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Renegade Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="renegade_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>One of a few exoskeletons assembled by the Renegades back in 2011 to help secure their final push into Clear Sky's base. Unfortunately, they were virtually wiped out before their final victory ever came, thanks to the interference of a Mercenary with a trench coat and a marksman rifle. Modern Renegades who wear this armor always go into battle like a man possessed, eager to mete vengeance upon their most hated foes.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="isg_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Exoskeleton</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>The official version of the UNISG exoskeleton released in limited quantities by special order of the United Nations. While it still possesses many of the design flaws of other exoskeletons, it's nonetheless seen as a great alternative to light command and scout vehicles.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="greh_exo_outfit_name">
		<text>Vyraj Power Armor</text>
	</string>
	<string id="greh_exo_outfit_description">
		<text>High-tech armor consisting of a steel-reinforced Kevlar jumpsuit and a tactical vest with Class IV inserts, all carried by powered limbs and servomotors. Study samples have revealed that its servos are made of alloys and materials unknown to any field of science in any other part of the world. Wearing this suit creates an unnatural feeling of bliss and calm within the wearer, although whether this sense of security is genuine or not remains to be understood.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>


<!-- Nosorog exskeletal armor -->
	<string id="dolg_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>PSZ-10d Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="merc_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Mercenary Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="army_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Military Stalker Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="monolith_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Monolith Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	<string id="isg_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>UNISG Nosorog</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="nosorog_outfit_description">
		<text>A next generation exoskeleton, consisting of a doubly reinforced Exosuit. Rumored to have been the brainchild of a now-deceased stalker named "Fang", whose designs were later claimed by all sorts of powerful factions across the Zone. If regular exoskeletons allow stalkers to feel like a light vehicle, the Nosorog almost makes them believe they're a main battle tank, able to withstand incredible punishment while carrying tremendous ordnance.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="freedom_nosorog_outfit_name">
		<text>Champion of Freedom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="freedom_nosorog_outfit_desc">
		<text>A next generation exoskeleton, consisting of a doubly reinforced Exosuit. Rumored to have been the brainchild of a now-deceased stalker named "Fang", whose designs were later claimed by all sorts of powerful factions across the Zone. If regular exoskeletons allow stalkers to feel like a light vehicle, the Nosorog almost makes them believe they're a main battle tank, able to withstand incredible punishment while carrying tremendous ordnance.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

<!-- No group -->	
	<string id="ghillie_outfit_name">
		<text>Ghillie Suit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ghillie_outfit_description">
		<text>This suit is designed to simulate a ‘heap of foliage.’ Usually this type of suit is worn by snipers and hunters to blend in with the environment and hide themselves from enemies. Ghillie suits are commercially produced, but usually both military personnel and civilians customize and improve them to suit their needs.\n \n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>