<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies">
		<text>Anomalies</text>
	</string>

<!--
	STORMS
-->

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_emission">
		<text>Emission</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_emission_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Emissions %c[ui_gray_2], also known as %c[pda_green]Blowouts%c[ui_gray_2], are sudden releases of massive amounts of radiation.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Strong winds, storm clouds and a scarlet red sky all appear with the onset of an emission, followed by numerous eruptions of thunder and a deep rumbling. These events begin with a sharp surge in radioactive and psychic activity and end with destroying most life as waves of radiation envelope the Zone.\n \n
		Despite being extremely deadly, it is still quite easy to survive an emission by taking cover within buildings or underground tunnels until the event has run its course.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] Much in the same way as a psy-storm, the massive amount of energy released by an emission appears to "%c[pda_white]recharge%c[ui_gray_2]" many anomalies, allowing stalkers to farm new artefacts from them.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_psistorm">
		<text>Psy-storm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_psistorm_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Psy-storms %c[ui_gray_2]consist of multiple psy-vortices, which release lethal amounts of psychic energy.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]These unusual weather anomalies are a very recent arrival to the Zone. Beginning with a purple/pink haze and large formations of storm clouds, it takes very little time for a psy-storm to form and start wreaking havoc upon the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] Similar to emissions, the massive amount of energy dispersed by a psy-storm appears to "%c[pda_white]recharge%c[ui_gray_2]" many anomalies, allowing stalkers to farm new artefacts from them.	
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	OTHER
-->

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_brain_scorcher">
		<text>Brain Scorcher</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_brain_scorcher_text">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_green]Brain Scorcher %c[ui_gray_2]is a former military installation that was seized by the group and became the first major application of mind control technology in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]After the Soviet Union's dissolution, the Group continued the research started in Lab X-8 and adapted the installation at the Scorcher, or most importantly, the Lab X-19 located in an old bunker underneath the facility.\n \n
		When the Zone was created, the Scorcher was activated by the Common Consciousness in order to obstruct the way into the center of the Zone. The psy-emissions generated by the installation were effective at mind controlling trespassers and subjecting them to the will of the collective, creating mindless zombified stalkers out of some and raw recruits for the Monolith faction out of others.\n \n
		While the majority of stalkers who came too close to the Brain Scorcher became zombies, a group of stalkers known as Strelok's Group were able to slip past the Brain Scorcher (most likely with the help of Guide) and reach the center of the Zone. The path to the Scorcher and the installation itself is heavily guarded by the fanatical Monolith.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_phantom">
		<text>Phantom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_phantom_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Phantoms %c[ui_gray_2]are illusory beings that exist within the mind, rather than the physical realm.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Whilst difficult to classify as either an anomaly or a mutant, a phantom is an involuntary mental projection of a mutant currently found somewhere within the Zone. These projections are always accompanied by an audible "howling" noise and appear glowing and transparent, gradually floating toward the victim through walls and across the air.\n \n
		It is unknown why they only take the form of mutants, including those of which a stalker has never encountered, and as to why they never take the appearance of those that are now extinct, such as the Tark. A leading theory of this phenomenon suggests that the Zone's living mutants are in some way strongly connected to the Noosphere, and that through this a psy-field unintentionally imprints their visual appearance and hostile nature into the minds of its victims.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_psi">
		<text>Psy-field</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_psi_text">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Very large areas of psy-activity that ascend up to the clouds and are often only visible by columns of distorted light.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]These fields have harmful effects on brain tissue, and sometimes could be a visible sign of a psy-emission, causing light to heavy damage. However, most of the time these columns contain pools of anomalies or, if no anomalies are present, are instead coupled with high levels of radiation.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2]Unlike Emissions and Psy-storms, Psy-fields do not spawn "recharge" anomalies to spawn artefacts.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_radiation">
		<text>Radiation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_radiation_text">
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]An area of increased radiation, typically over 50 milliRoentgen per hour (mR/h). Staying in a radiation zone for long periods of time is strongly discouraged as it can cause radiation sickness and eventually even death.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Tips\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] The %c[pda_white]Geiger Counter %c[ui_gray_2]is an essential tool for detecting and measuring ionizing radiation. The more rapid the clicking, the more radiation detected.\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] A lot of stalkers die due to radiation sickness. It is highly advised to keep a packet of %c[pda_white]Anti-radiation Drugs %c[ui_gray_2]on you.\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] Make sure that your gas mask is always in good condition.\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[pda_white] Vodka %c[ui_gray_2]and %c[pda_white]Cigarettes %c[ui_gray_2]are widely used among stalkers as a cheap yet considerable alternative to Anti-radiation Drugs.
		</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	FLAME
-->

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_burner">
		<text>Burner</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_burner_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Burner %c[ui_gray_2]is a stationary proximity-actitivated pillar of fire.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n	
		%c[ui_gray_2]A barely visible cloud of hot air that, when disturbed, shoots out a tall pillar of flame with heat reaching up to temperatures approaching 1000°C. At night it can be revealed by powerful detectors or by throwing objects into it, like bolts or spend casings.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Flame-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,255,0,0]Difficult\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,255,0,0]High
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_comet">
		<text>Comet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_comet_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Comet %c[ui_gray_2]is a dangerous mobile fire anomaly that reaches temperatures near that of the area around the sun.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The Comet anomaly functions much like a Burner anomaly, reaching temperatures of up to 5000+°C, dealing fire damage on close contact, but unlike the Burner, the Comet is mobile, hovering within a fixed area at a rapid pace.
		The Comet anomaly, unlike the Burner, is extremely powerful: it can kill even a well-armoured stalker if he gets hit directly.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Flame-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,255,255,0]Moderate\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,255,0,0]Extremely High\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] This anomaly does not spawn any kind of artefact.
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	CHEMICAL
-->

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_fuzz">
		<text>Burnt Fuzz</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_fuzz_text"> 	
		<text>The Burnt Fuzz anomaly is a vine-like formation that is capable of causing burns on organic objects that rapidly move through it.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]One of the Zone's examples of mutated vegetation, "Burnt Fuzz" resembles moss or vines that hang down like curtains. The anomaly only seems to react to rapidly approaching living organisms by discharging a cloud of incredibly small projectiles severely irritating or injuring uncovered or lightly protected skin upon contact.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Chemical-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,0,255,0]Easy\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,0,255,0]Low
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_fruit">
		<text>Fruit Punch</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_fruit_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Fruit Punch %c[ui_gray_2]is a puddle of extremely corrosive lambent green liquid.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]A puddle of liquid easily visible in almost any environment due it its bright glow and distinctive hissing and bubbling noises. On contact with the skin, it inflicts injuries similar to chemical burns caused by strong acids.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Chemical-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,0,255,0]Easy\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,0,255,0]Low
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gas">
		<text>Gas</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gas_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Gas %c[ui_gray_2]anomaly is recognizable by floating acidic green gas clouds wandering over the ground.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]When the gas comes into contact with metal parts or organic tissue, it emits and splashes out highly acidic compounds into its vicinity. It should not to be confused with the Fruit Punch anomaly, as it behaves more like a cloud or fog rather than a puddle of liquid.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Chemical-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,0,255,0]Easy\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,0,255,0]Low
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gascloud">
		<text>Gas Cloud</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_gascloud_text"> 	
		<text>The Gas Cloud anomaly resembles a Gas anomaly but is mobile and more potent. As such, it is the chemical counterpart to the Comet and Tesla anomalies.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Even while wearing a top-tier protective suit and even some chemical-protection artefacts, extended contact from this anomaly can cause serious injury or even instant death. If no alternative options are available, running through it as fast as you can is the best thing to do.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Chemical-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,255,255,0]Moderate\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,255,255,0]Moderate\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] This anomaly does not spawn any kind of artefact.
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	ELECTRIC
-->

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_electro">
		<text>Electro</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_electro_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Electro %c[ui_gray_2]anomaly holds no distinction for what crosses its event horizon, be it human, mutants or inanimate object.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]An anomalous formation, roughly 10 meters in diameter, accumulating large quantities of static electricity. When triggered, the anomaly bursts out in dozens of miniature electrical explosions, causing electric shock nearly always lethal to all living organisms. Recognizable by the bluish fog hovering above it, it may be avoided by carefully timing its moments of inactivity and moving through it or revealed by throwing objects such as bolts or spent casings into it.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Electricity-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,255,255,0]Moderate\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,255,0,0]High
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_pulse">
		<text>Pulse</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_pulse_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]Scientists believe that the %c[pda_white]Pulse %c[ui_gray_2]anomaly is a unique formation of thunderbolts under the aggressive effect of psy-waves within Zone borders.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Beginning with a blue haze, it takes very little time for a Pulse to form and discharge into the ground, leading to instant death for anything close enough to the point of impact. The frequency of this anomaly is directly connected to the weather, as it has a higher chance of forming during rain and storms. Although its kill radius is not as wide as a full psy-storm, the Pulse remains a credible threat. If a Pulse starts forming near you, run away as fast as you can.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Electricity-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,255,255,0]Moderate\n
		%c[pda_white]Danger: %c[0,255,0,0]Extremely High\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] This anomaly does not spawn any kind of artefact.
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_tesla">
		<text>Tesla</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_tesla_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Tesla %c[ui_gray_2]is a 5 billion joule mobile ball of electricity, much like a moving lightning strike.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]It is said that the Tesla anomaly is an evolved or greater form of an Electro anomaly. It's possible that a particularly large or intense Electro went undisturbed or built up a massive charge for an extensive amount of time and became mobile as a result, either to discharge its built up energy or to 'hunt' for targets or prey. Those struck by this ball of energy can expect serious injuries or death.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Electricity-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,255,0,0]High\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,255,0,0]High\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] This anomaly does not spawn any kind of artefact.
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	GRAVITY
-->

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_springboard">
		<text>Springboard</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_springboard_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Springboard %c[ui_gray_2]is an unstable gravitational field inflicting heavy damage to anyone within its radius.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Remains active for a week on average with the amount of damage inflicted changing during its lifetime, ranging from minor bruises, to serious wounds to even instant death. Easy to spot in daylight, this anomaly is accompanied by air fluctuations, dancing leaves and distinctive crimson-colored stains on the ground. The "Springboard" can also be revealed by throwing objects such as bolts or spent casings into it.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Gravity-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,0,255,0]Easy\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,0,255,0]Low %c[pda_white]to %c[0,255,0,0]High
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_vortex">
		<text>Vortex</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_vortex_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Vortex %c[ui_gray_2]is a gravitational nature that is capable of constricting matter into an incredibly tight space before violently exploding.\n \n 
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]An anomaly of gravitational nature, when triggered, the tremendous power of the Vortex anomaly drags everything within the radius of 10-15 meters towards its center. Victims drawn into the core have no chance of survival as their bodies are often quickly constricted into a tight lump, only to be blown up in a powerful discharge of energy. Easily recognizable in daylight by the air fluctuation above, dancing leaves, fragments of dismembered corpses lying around and a distinctive dark stain in its center. Highly dangerous at night since it can be revealed only by means of a detector or by throwing objects into it.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Gravity-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,255,255,0]Moderate\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,255,255,0]Moderate %c[pda_white]to %c[0,255,0,0]High
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_whirligig">
		<text>Whirligig</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_whirligig_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Whirligig %c[ui_gray_2]anomaly snatches its victims up in the air and spins them at breakneck speed.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The exact nature of the "Whirligig" remains unknown. The anomaly can be recognized by a light whirlwind of dust above. Victims caught on its outer rim can escape with relatively minor injuries though those caught within are thrown up into the air and spun at breakneck speeds. After a short period of time, the anomaly releases a discharge powerful enough to dismember the victim through sheer force. until the anomaly eventually discharges.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Gravity-based\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[0,0,255,0]Easy\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[0,0,255,0]Low to %c[0,255,0,0]High
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	REALITY
-->

	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_space">
		<text>Space</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_space_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Space %c[ui_gray_2]anomaly is the ultimate result of the Zone's instability as it alters the very fabric of reality, distorting time and space.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Miniature wormholes which teleport anything that enters it to another location. This theory of teleportation seems to be proven upon talking to a stalker at the Cordon by the rail bridge. Asking him about the 'black hole' will direct you to the Space anomaly there which he and his friends have been apparently throwing trash into and recalls seeing the same trash later in an old tunnel.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Reality-altering\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[pda_white]N.A.\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[pda_white]Unknown\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] This anomaly does not spawn any kind of artefact.
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_teleport">
		<text>Teleport</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_anomalies_teleport_text"> 	
		<text>%c[ui_gray_2]The %c[pda_white]Teleport %c[ui_gray_2]is a rare anomaly found in a few locations throughout the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_green]Information:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Harmless in nature, anything that comes into contact with the Teleport anomaly is instantly teleported to another location.\n \n
		%c[pda_blue]Notes:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Type: %c[d_orange]Reality-altering\n
		%c[pda_white] • Avoidability: %c[pda_white]N.A.\n
		%c[pda_white] • Danger: %c[pda_white]Unknown\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] This anomaly does not spawn any kind of artefact.
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>