<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<string_table>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options">
		<text>Options</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_ai_die_to_anomalies">
		<text>AI Die to Anomalies</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_ai_die_to_anomalies_text">
		<text>[pda_white]Removes anomalies as a factor in the AI's pathfinding.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With this feature enabled, mutants and other stalkers will no longer know exactly where anomalies are located. As such, they will now find themselves placed at the full mercy of the Zone's environment, no different from your own character.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_aoe_pickup_mode">
		<text>AoE Pickup Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_aoe_pickup_mode_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Enables picking up multiple items at once with a single key-press.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_artefact_degradation">
		<text>Artefact Degradation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_artefact_degradation_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Causes artefact abilities and bonuses to degrade when activated.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With this feature enabled, having the best artefacts is no-longer the end game for artefact hunters as they will become weaker the more they are used, promoting their further hunting and accumulation, instead of becoming just a quick source of income.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is enabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_delayed_repairs">
		<text>Delayed Repairs</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_delayed_repairs_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Allows technicians to retain your equipment while they are theoretically repairing it.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With this feature enabled, broken weapons, outfits, and other items brought to a technician will be kept in their possession until they have completed all repairs. After handing over your items you can speak with the technician to ask whether they are ready for pick-up, to which they will either return them or tell you how much time is still required. This adds a somewhat realistic enhancement to the traditional repair system and is suitable if you are seeking a more difficult experience, as it will no-longer work instantaneously.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_enhanced_recoil">
		<text>Enhanced Recoil</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_enhanced_recoil_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Adds much more varied and realistic handling of weapons.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With this feature enabled, a much more randomized and multi-directional recoil is created when firing your weapon. This restores the challenge of mastering your weapon and makes your choice of upgrades and ammunition much more influential.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]It is highly recommended to only enable this feature if your system can maintain at least a steady 30fps, although 50+ is much more preferable. This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_hardcore_ai_aim">
		<text>Hardcore AI Aim</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_hardcore_ai_aim_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Increases AI aim predictability and decreases reaction times.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With this feature enabled, it becomes harder for you to avoid being hit whilst strafing and sprinting, with the use of cover becoming much more essential for long-term survival.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_helicopter_patrols">
		<text>Helicopter Patrols</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_helicopter_patrols_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Enables the use of air support by factions to defend strategic areas.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Factions who have friendly aircraft patrolling in the area will be able to call on them for support in attacking, or defence from enemy stalkers (including you) and mutants. Despite their intimidating appearance, they can be easily taken down after receiving light damage to the tail rotor.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]LOCATIONS:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] Agroprom\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] Cordon\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] Darkscape\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] Great Swamp\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2] Limansk\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2]These features can be toggled from the game options menu and are enabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_localisation">
		<text>Localization</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_localisation_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Allows setting the language of the game.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Upon changing your localization, the majority of text will update automatically, however some will still require a game restart to change.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]SUPPORTED LANGUAGES:\n
		%c[pda_white] • English: %c[ui_gray_2] ENG\n
		%c[pda_white] • Russian: %c[ui_gray_2] RUS\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be adjusted from the game options menu and is set to "ENG" by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_lootmoney">
		<text>Loot Money On Corpses</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_lootmoney_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Allows finding money in the pockets of those who have died.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]The amount of money you find depends on the rank of the dead stalker. The higher the rank, the more money that may be be found.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the gameplay options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_online_exclusion">
		<text>Online Exclusion</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_online_exclusion_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Creates a no-spawn zone around your character.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]As you explore near the edge of levels and their entry/exit points, you could be attacked by enemies arriving from other locations. With online exclusion enabled, these spawns are delayed until you are safely out of the way.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]It should be noted that this system revolves entirely around you; any enemies already at a location whilst you are changing levels will not be de-spawned upon your arrival. This feature can be adjusted from the game options menu and is set to 25 by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_population_factors">
		<text>Population Factors</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_population_factors_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Modify the number of stalkers and mutants found in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Stalker and mutant population factors can be adjusted independently of one another, allowing to decide how wild or settled the Zone should be without the need to modify any of the game's files.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]It should be noted that the effect is greatest when starting a new character. If these factors are changed during a playthrough, they will only take effect as stalkers and/or mutants die and respawn in greater or smaller numbers. These features can be adjusted from the game options menu and are set to 0.5 by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_quicksave_count">
		<text>Quicksave Count</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_quicksave_count_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Allows the game to cycle between multiple quicksaves.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]When making a quicksave, the filename will be appended with a number on the end. These numbers are used by the game to help with the tracking of multiple different quicksaves.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be adjusted from the game options menu and is set to 5 by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_radio_music">
		<text>Radio Music</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_radio_music_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Allows for custom music tracks to be played at certain locations.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Certain areas within the Zone have radios installed, with each playing a selection of musical tracks to keep stalkers entertained.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]LOCATIONS:\n
		%c[pda_white] • Agroprom: %c[ui_gray_2] Military Base\n
		%c[pda_white] • Cordon: %c[ui_gray_2] Sidorovich's Bunker\n
		%c[pda_white] • Great Swamp: %c[ui_gray_2] Clear Sky Base\n
		%c[pda_white] • Dark Valley: %c[ui_gray_2] Bandit Base\n
		%c[pda_white] • Rostok: %c[ui_gray_2] 100 Rads Bar\n
		%c[pda_white] • Red Forest: %c[ui_gray_2] Forester's Tower\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is enabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_sleep_deprivation">
		<text>Sleep Simulation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_sleep_deprivation_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Allows time and the use of consumables to fatigue your character.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Throughout the Zone you will find many beds and sleeping bags. Normally they are only used to allow skipping time by sleeping, however with this feature enabled they become an essential part of gameplay. Tiredness can be accelerated through consuming items such as medical kits and vodka, and negated with items such as high-caffeine energy drinks.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_thirst">
		<text>Thirst Simulation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_thirst_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]A hardcore option to simulate thirst.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This option pushes the player to constantly look for water sources and adds another layer of difficulty. A thirst indicator will display on your HUD to determine your thirst level.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is enabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>`
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_dynamic_news">
		<text>Dynamic News</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_dynamic_news_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Allows stalkers to report on their experiences in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Stalkers will comment on events that they have seen or heard near their location or on their current adventures using the PDA communications network. These events and activities can range from something as mundane as complaining about the price of goods sold by a trader, to requesting help from faction allies when under attack.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the UI/HUD options menu and is enabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_extended_hud">
		<text>Extended HUD</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_extended_hud_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Allows the display of additional on-screen information.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With this feature enabled, brief companion information and a miniaturized version of the artefact belt are made visible on the heads-up display.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the UI/HUD options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_portrait_by_outfit">
		<text>Portrait by Outfit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_portrait_by_outfit_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Changes your portrait based on your current outfit.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]With this feature enabled, every time you equip or unequip an outfit (not including headgear) your character's portrait will be updated to reflect this, mimicking how portraits for the AI match how they look.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the Gameplay/General options menu and is disabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_use_battery">
		<text>Battery Use</text>
	</string>
	<string id="encyclopedia_options_use_battery_text">
		<text>%c[pda_white]Requires batteries to keep gadgets functional.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]INFORMATION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]Electrical devices such as detectors and flashlights require batteries in order to work properly. This will make it necessary to always make sure you have spare batteries available.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]ATTENTION:\n
		%c[ui_gray_2]This feature can be toggled from the game options menu and is enabled by default.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>